Hello, beautiful people. Are we ready to
rock? My name is June U and I've been
creating content now for the last six
years. And in that midst, I've struggled
in many different ways. I've struggled
with the fear of being seen. I struggled
with a lot of insecurity. I struggled
with what my friends and family were to
say about me. I struggled with passive
aggressive statements in group chats of
people saying, "Ah, June is trying too
hard." I've seen my posts be sent into
group chats. Like, I've seen that. I've
had these insecurities of me thinking
that I didn't have a story to tell. I
thought that my life wasn't interesting
enough. I grew up poor. I had nothing
interest. I was a biomedical engineering
student. Like that's not really
interesting. And I had all of these
insecurities. I turned that ultimately
into my first post that turned into a
second, a third, a fourth, a fifth. And
then now 6 years later, I have over 8
million followers across my platforms.
I've done $10 million in the last 12
months alone. I've worked with some of
the biggest brands in the world from
Meta to Medy Chat to Red Bull and I get
to speak on stages and I get to spread
the good news. Really, the goal of today
is to teach you exactly what to post.
Then I'm going to go straight into the
how, like, how do you physically put the
post together? I got you covered. Like,
I'm going to give you some templates.
I'm going to make this super easy. This
is from the ground up trying to give you
all the resources I possibly can. But
that being said, I think we're ready to
go. Ladies and gentlemen, I want to
welcome you in officially to how to turn
your story into content. I have poured
hundreds of hours into what you're about
to see today. What I can guarantee you
is you have never seen any of the things
that I am teaching you today anywhere
else. This is not regurgitated
information. This is how to tell stories
people can't stop watching from a
practitioner himself. Okay? I am not
going to be teaching you theory here.
I'm going to show you exactly what to
post and I'm going to break them down
into templates. So, even if you are a
very beginner, you'll know exactly what
to do coming out of here today. I want
you to win. I desperately want to see
you win. And I hope that you tag me in
your stories. I hope that you DM me
because I want to support you. Let's do
this. I'm about to make a claim. Most of
you are going to disagree with. It does
not matter what industry you're
currently in. It does not matter how
boring you think your life is. It does
not matter whether you've got four or
40,000 followers. You already possess
the most important asset of 2026, your
story. By now, you already know your
story is the one asset AI cannot fake,
buy, or steal from you. But having a
good story was never the hard part.
Turning it into content you can post,
even when you really do not feel like
it, when your energy is at its lowest
point, that's the part nobody shares.
And that's the actual reason most people
who already know their story still
aren't posting. Now, why am I so
passionate about this? Well, it's
because I have no business being in
front of you right now. You see, I had
immigrated from Korea to the US when I
was just 3 years old. I was raised by a
single dad. When my parents got
divorced, they got divorced over the
phone. And my mom, who was my best
friend at the time, left to a completely
different country and I lost contact
with her for over 10 years.
We were constantly moving from home to
home until we landed in a tiny
apartment. And in that apartment, it was
my brother and I sharing a small room
and my dad sleeping on the living room
floor. I tell you that because I
certainly didn't grow up with
connections or a silver platter. I
didn't grow up with a ton of
opportunity. No, I just saw a ton of
suffering. In all honesty, my dad worked
14-hour days in construction in the
brutal heat. And that's my reality while
being in middle school, while being in
high school, and some of my most
important developmental years. So,
although I might have not had a lot of
the tangible benefit, I did have this
unbelievable drive to do something
different. And ultimately, it was that
ambition that enabled me to tell my
story. You see, I didn't have more
experience than you. I guarantee it.
There's no way. Cuz when I first
started, I was a broke college kid, lost
in life. I didn't really have many
friends either, so trust me, there's no
way that I had more skills than you.
What I did have though was the ability
just to show up and tell my story. And
it was the smallest transformations that
I started with. It was the smallest
milestones, the smallest glimpses of my
purpose, my smallest ambitions, my
smallest struggles. And as I did that
over a long period of time,
interestingly enough, I found my people.
Today, I sit at over 8 million followers
across my platforms. I've generated $10
million in the last 12 months alone.
I've worked with Red Bull, ManyHat, and
Meta. I get invited to events and travel
the world. I was just speaking on the
main stage at Kan Line, the same stage
that Steven Bartlett and Mel Robbins
spoke at. I'm the co-founder of Creative
College. I've started my own podcast.
And I've done all of this on the backs
of simply telling my story. So, you're
going to hear it in my voice how
seriously I take this because I
desperately want to see you win. And I
thought that there was no better way to
actually show you this than ultimately
through content. I had deep insecurities
which I believe stem from having such a
different upbringing than those around
me. My family immigrated from Korea to
the US when I was 3 years old. My
parents never spoke English. My dad
[music] worked construction 12 hours a
day and my mom worked as a nail tack.
But no matter how hard they tried, we
found ourselves in hundreds of thousands
[music] of dollars in debt. When I was
just 13, my mom, who was my best friend
at the time, left overnight to a
different country permanently, and
[music] I lost contact with her for 10
years. My parents divorced over the
phone and our financial troubles
worsened until we had to sell our
childhood home and move five [music]
times in just a few years into smaller
and smaller homes. Eventually, my
brother and I shared a small room and my
dad slept on the living room floor.
Through it all, I I felt this great
calling to be the one to provide for my
family. So, I did everything I could. I
went from troubled student [music] in
high school to being at the top of my
class as I was getting my bachelor's and
masters in biomedical engineering
simultaneously. I worked odd jobs like
being [music] a server and trying to
find ways to earn for my family. And
then in 2020, Tik Tok gave rise to short
form content. So I jumped on that
opportunity although very nervous
considering [music] I had no creative
nor business background. In fact,
biomedical engineering could not be a
[music] more polar opposite field. So,
there was this constant dilemma where I
didn't feel confident posting and at the
same time passive aggressive comments
like you're trying too [music] hard or
you still doing that influencer thing or
a norm. I first started with fashion and
fitness content because I thought they
were the cool things to do. I tried
every trend but still found myself
[music] in the 200 view jail. However,
the one thing I promised myself was that
I would show up regardless. And after
posting daily for a year, I finally saw
some traction. But I decided I wanted to
make meaningful content and [music]
start helping people. And this is when I
started to use everything I've learned
as an engineer to create a data-driven
[music] content system. This made
showing up daily easy. And ultimately,
it was that system that brought me into
my first 100,000, [music] 1 million, and
5 million followers. I was also able to
use that system to monetize. First was
my guide to academic [music] success,
which earned $100,000 for four
consecutive months. Then the learning
system book, which landed number one on
Amazon's new releases [music] and
skyrocketed the business to over a
million dollars in just 10 months. I was
still a student throughout this entire
[music] time and I actually remember
sitting in my classroom when I saw that
$1 million notification. And now I
[music] find so much joy in helping
other creators win. Watching someone go
from insecure to finally finding their
voice. From doubting themselves to
seeing their first million views. From
working overtime [music] to creating a
life where they can be more present with
the people they love. Whether it's moms,
working professionals, business owners,
[music] or coaches, I truly believe
everyone has a story worth sharing. and
I have the most fun [music] helping turn
those stories into meaningful and
transformational content. It's hard to
explain, but [music] seeing their face
light up when it finally clicks, that
feeling is truly addicting. [music] Of
course, my own journey has given me the
opportunity to build incredible
businesses and [music] work with amazing
brands, which I am forever grateful for.
But the biggest win is being able
[music] to serve others and help them
win, too. I know how hard it is. So, if
I can alleviate any of the pain, it is
my [music] greatest honor because when
one person finds their voice, it doesn't
just change their life. It touches
[music] thousands of others they will
reach with their content. And that
ripple is what makes all of this
meaningful. You deserve to win. And I
would do whatever it takes to get you
there. I can't help but smile when I see
it because everything I've ever wanted
is this. To be able to share what I've
learned along the way, to help you avoid
the mistakes that I've made. I wish I
wish that somebody would have done this
for me earlier. I wish that somebody
would have shortcut this process for me
because why can't we all win? I think
so. Why can't we all win? Why? I think
you deserve to win. My whole life, my
entire family has been looked down upon
and I don't want you guys to feel that
way. I want to be sure that all of you
guys come out of here knowing exactly
what to post, when to post it, and how
to do it, too. So, 6 years ago, I
certainly had a very, very big problem.
You see, my desires and my reality were
not meeting. I genuinely do not think my
audience is filled with get-richqu
people. Like, I don't think that's my
audience. I think all of you guys are
people that really do care that you do
this the right way. Like, who the heck
cares if you have a 100,000 followers
and you've done it through trends and
it's meaningless content. I would argue
the person that has 4,000 followers who
had done it the right way would feel
more fulfilled in the process. So,
that's what I wanted. Like, even while
back then I knew that, right? I think we
all know that. But the honest truth was
that I'm going to be fully fully fully
transparent. I was super insecure, like
very insecure. I had a lot of acne. I
had a lot of things about my life where
I grew up without many people looking
like me. I was always constantly judged
anyways. And so this idea of being
visible, failing in public, potentially
getting more scrutinized was not was not
a reality that I wanted. And so
therefore, I had to do the thing at
least that I felt was the safer route
through this process of content. like
what was the route that everyone that
was telling me to do? So, I chose that
one, which was literally to post one
thing, right? So, like I genuinely hate
the idea of niching down. Those words
get me so annoyed. It's like, oh, stay
in your lane. Like, do the thing.
[sighs]
But back then, but back then, I didn't
know better. So, I I did the exact same
thing. Like, I fully get you. So, I at
least thought, let me teach something
that I think is cool. So, I taught
fashion. And this is what my content
looked like. This is what I did in the
very beginning. So this is like baby
June
[music]
>> super speed sonic I'm running super
super super speed sonic I'm running
>> parents basement brother's clothes I had
no business doing this but it's just
because these stupid gurus told me that
I am only one thing to I thought I had
to choose the thing right so that's
where I was and in that reality I look
like every other creator and I hated
that. So I hated the idea that I wasn't
growing, that I had zero unique
perspective, that I had no clear
identity. And for those folks that are
new to Instagram, you might not know
this, but those that are a bit more
experienced, of course you do. But the
number of posts here are only indicative
of what is on your main profile grid. So
if you actually move it over to your
reels tab only, it doesn't count. But
this was like 15 months worth of posting
every single day. And I was losing
followers. Like you post something and
you literally lose followers as a result
of it. It's like what the heck? This is
the opposite of what I thought content
was about. Everyone's telling me to post
consistently. I'm doing it and I'm
losing followers. I don't know. I was
very frustrated in that experience. At a
certain point, I said enough is enough.
I decided to stop trying to copy
everyone else and start posting who I
actually was. And there was freedom in
that, right? So before I was trying to
fit into a single niche. I was copying
what worked for others. I was chasing
trends. I was trying to build an
audience who cared more about the topic
than me. But after I actually started
posting what I cared about. I started
sharing my perspective. I started
posting my reality which was as a
student which is certainly not that
interesting. But I was then able to
build an audience who champions me. So
as I evolved from being a student to
then being a business owner, those
people still came with me throughout the
entire process. The honest truth is that
I started telling my story. How many of
you guys have ever been in school
before? middle school, high school,
college, grad school. So, literally all
of us, right? How many of you guys hated
it? Thought it was the most mundane,
boring thing that you wish that you
didn't have to do. Me, too. How many of
you guys thought to record yourselves
doing it and build an audience as a
resultant of it? Probably none of you.
So, what I had done by telling my story
was not live a more interesting life. It
was doubling down on the things that I
was already doing. And that's the power
of storytelling. It's not about waiting
to be somebody. you already are someone
and it's about finding meaning in the
smallest moments and I developed a
repeatable system that allowed me to do
that at scale. So eventually this is
what happened. I built a personal brand
that was built on me and not a specific
niche. And now I have real impact on
people around me. Like is this not cool?
Like I look at this stock I'm like are
you kidding me? This is like a dream
come true. I am proud of what I create
and post. When I look at my page I'm
like cool. Like I'm finally doing the
thing that actually is what I've dreamt
of while being younger. I'm aligned with
look this is me. This is me at an event
of mine and all the people that came to
my event. Like how cool is that? So I
get to achieve the things that I've
always wanted to achieve. And it's not
just me. Now I'm on a mission. I'm on a
mission to continuously help you guys do
the exact same thing. I've helped 10,000
people personally myself. People that
are just like you. Like how many of you
guys have never edited a post before?
How many of you guys have never done a
talking video before? How many of you
guys have never even started an
Instagram account before? Like, I get
it. Like, each one of these people were
like that. And they left with 2.7
million views, 2.4, 1.5, 4.7, 1.8, 19.1,
3.3, 3.9, 15.7, 2.6, 1.8 million views.
Just normal people dominating because
they've learned to tell their story. You
see what I want to do in the next two
slides is just a quick little context
for what storytelling can do for any
person. Okay, so this is a swoman,
right? So she had come into my program
and she had stated, okay, I've been
creating content for a while. So that's
what Yin had. So even though she was
close to about a year of posting, she
was stuck and plateaued. And I was like,
all right, what is it that you do? And
she was talking to me about the
practices with her sword. Like she
literally like wields a sword. And I'm
like, that's the coolest thing ever. But
when I look at the content, it was just
about that practice. And I asked her, I
was like, "Why do you do that practice?
Why? Like ultimately, what is the
reasoning underneath it?" And she's
like, "It makes me feel powerful as a
woman." I'm like, "Cool. We got
something. Let's tell that story."
[music]
>> Now she's at 91,000 followers and she
has 1.6 million, 1.2 million, and 1.2 2
million views. So, this was Yin and I'm
going to show you one more creator that
also did something similar. So, Ella
came in and she was posting for a while.
She had a lot of trial reels as well,
but she just wasn't growing. She
actually didn't grow for many months and
she started burning out as a resultant
of it. She was a trainer and she was
thinking about, of course, I'm just
going to make gym content, but I'm like,
"No, no, no. We have to actually tell a
story with the same gym clips." So, she
already had these clips that she
recorded in the gym. She just didn't
know how to tell the story behind it.
And I told her what else to film. And I
said, "All right, let's actually make
you feel human instead of you just
showing that you're very strong, instead
of showing that you're completely fit.
Like, what is the actual story behind
you?" And this is the post that we came
up with.
[music]
>> And now she's also at 119,000 followers.
But why does this post work?
Does that make sense? As in for all of
us, like even if you weren't trainer,
you might already have the B-roll, but
it means nothing if it isn't relevant to
people. Does that make sense? So, like,
yes, if you think that you're incredibly
fit, if you think that you're incredibly
smart, if you think that you are a very
good expert, it does not matter. It
literally does not matter. You know how
I can prove it? The smartest people in
the world are not the best creatives,
right? In fact, some of the best experts
in the world are the quietest and the
most invisible, and they're the ones not
making the money. However, the people
that are willing to share the story and
make it relevant to people, make it
human to people. That's where the
connection happens and that's why people
buy into people. And we're going to
break down all of that today. And I want
to make sure that you all build
something purposeful to you. So, think
about this. Think about this. This might
be the first time in a long time where
you're doing something for yourself. Not
your parents, not your bosses, not your
managers, not even for your kids or your
partners, but actually for yourself. And
I want to take a moment to celebrate
that and take a lot a lot of meaning in
it. I encourage you then to not
passively sit through this and think,
"All right, I should probably make the
most out of this experience. This guy is
spending the next 3 hours about to teach
me everything that he knows and what
he's calling the best teaching that he's
ever developed. I should probably not
just scroll away and actually become a
storyteller." But what bothers me is
that still like 95% of people become
scrollers. They're the ones that take
notes. Yes, of course they're going to
feel inspired because the teaching is
going to be very good. However, they're
going to close the tab and go back to
scrolling. But the storytellers, the
people that actually take the notes,
feel inspired, but post something, those
are the people that give me meaning in
this life. So, I want to go ahead and
speak to you what storytelling is, and
then ultimately we're going to go into
how to actually make it, like film it
and put it together and things like
that.
So storytelling boils down to
psychology, right? At the end of the
day, it is a human experience. And I
think the worst creators are anti-human.
Like they're just teaching and saying
the exact same information that you
could give from AI. Okay. What is
storytelling? This is how I define it.
This is how I define it to all of my
students and whenever I'm speaking on
stages. It's taking something you've
already lived and telling it so people
feel it and see themselves in you.
Why is it important is because
everything around us at your desk right
now wherever you are at work right now
is made up of stories. You see the books
around you, the music, the brands, the
conversations, history, places,
products, people, movies and TV. Every
single one of them is literally a story
and that's why you remember them.
There's a lot of books, movies, and TV
songs, brands, conversations that you
don't recall. Think about why that's the
case. We're about to break it down. A
lot of you guys right now think that you
live a boring life. The honest truth
though is that you've just never learned
how to read your life. And actually, I'm
now I'm being serious, but it's not your
fault. As in you, for so long, you've
dampened your voice. Not because you've
wanted to because every time you
actually spoke up for yourself, you were
told to be quiet. Every time you try to
say something, you were told it's not
your turn. You were told to stay in your
lane. So, of course, after a long period
of time, you actually ignore a lot of
the really beautiful parts about your
life. So, let's think about a car ride.
I got into a car. This is not even my
car, but [laughter] I got into a car for
the sake of the photo. And I want to
just walk you through a little bit about
how boring car ride could even turn into
stories and how there's so many stories
that we actually might ignore. So, if we
think about anyone in here go through
road rage? I love my girlfriend. She's
like the coolest, cutest, most adorable
human being ever, but she has road rage
and it's really funny. She's like a
small person and she has like a lot of
[laughter]
and so is it about that? Is it trying to
calm your nervous system while driving?
Is it about the favorite song that you
hear on the radio? Is it about the
landmarks that you recognize? Is it
about ruminating on what you do all of
this for? I tend to do a lot of this
like when I'm driving, I I tend to think
very very hard. Or maybe you see a car
that's driving by and you're like, "Oh,
I love that car. That's my dream car."
Or maybe you're somebody that is
constantly in your own thoughts and
you're you're somebody that is always
thinking about work. You're like, "hm,
what do I need to do today?" Whatever it
may be, all I'm trying to tell you is
that you have these stories that center
you. Like you have all of these stories
no matter where you go and it's up to us
to find them, to tell the best versions
of them, and to make meaning in them. I
love who loves Disney movies. Hope I'm
not the only one who loves Korean street
food. This is doubleg spicy rice cakes.
Who in here loves widelegg pants? Who in
here loves coldplays yellow? I love
these four things. And it's not because
that they're the best things in the
entire world, as in like the best
produced things or the most expensive
things or the newest things. No, it's
because they made me feel something,
right? Disney movies remind me of my
childhood. Korean food reminds me of my
sister's cooking. Widelegg pants. So, I
used to have these. I still have them.
I'm actually like kind of wearing one
right now. But these widelegg pants, my
girlfriend complimented them when I
first met her and Cole plays yellow. My
bus driver, Mr. Thomas, while I was in
elementary school, shout out to you. He
basically would hum this song all the
time. That's where I got introduced to
it.
Now that we have talked about how
storytelling makes you feel something
and that's why you remember it. Who in
here has been told to stay in your lane,
do one thing, teach one thing, pick an
industry or problem, just stay. But yes,
okay. I I I get it. Like I was there,
too.
But the honest truth is that I really do
think like niching down is the most
antihuman thing that you can do because
we're not one thing. The most boring
people that I know are still not one
thing, right? Like you're made up of
multi different facets. I actually
believe that you're made up of four
pillars. It's life, love, identity,
fitness, earnings.
Love, L, identity, I fitness, E,
earnings. What did June just come out
with an acronym that spells out life to
tell us that stories come from our life
and he's going to actually tell us that
these categories of our life turn into
the best stories? Yeah, you darn bet I
did do that. Um, so L I F E. It's easy
to remember. And this is my storytelling
wheel. Again, L I F E. It should be easy
to remember. Now, this storytelling
wheel achieves two things. One, it
actually helps you find your stories. L
I F E. Love, identity, fitness, and
earnings. Love could be relationships
and hobbies. I could be culture, sex,
and age. And faith. And fitness could be
mind, body, and spirit. Earnings could
be career, clients, and skills. We'll go
over that. Not as important yet. But
number two, find the meaning. Basically,
there are three layers to how you can
tell something. What is safe is what you
all think of. And you think that that is
how content should be, but it's not
true. Safe is generic. Safe is like AI
and that will never win. Everyone online
is doing safe. What is real is that it's
relatable. It's the underlying emotion.
But raw is the best. It's engaging. It's
it's here that the best creators live.
And I'm going to show you how you can
turn a moment into the raw
expression of it. Okay.
So again, L, love, what you love,
relationships and hobbies. I for
identity, who you are, your origin
story, your culture, sex, age, faith,
fitness, mind, body, and spirit, health,
routines. E, earnings could be your
career, client skills. Even if you are
unemployed, great, wonderful. That's
okay. You can talk about being
unemployed or you could be talking about
you finding a new job or starting a
business or you can talk about your old
job. It doesn't matter.
So, let's talk about how to use the
storytelling wheel. Okay, so for all of
you, when you're using the storytelling
wheel, you're going to start off with
the moment and you're going to put it on
the outside of the wheel.
Okay? It could be any moment. Even the
smallest moments, good doesn't have to
be a big moment.
And we're going to try to craft meaning
out of it. So again, storytelling is not
about having an impressive life. It's
not about traveling more. It's not about
making more money. It's not about being
more successful or more famous.
Storytelling is about finding meaning in
the already lived experiences. It's
about being you. So, if you're quiet,
it's okay. Be quiet. Stop trying to
pretend to be somebody else. You don't
have to. And I want to show you how you
can do this. So, let's say we take a
moment. You're going to ask yourself why
three times. The moment, then ask
yourself why three times. Because after
each, you go one layer deeper into this
wheel. Eventually, you're going to get
to the raw. And that is ultimately uh
the goal.
These each layers are going to be the
obvious reason then the feeling
underneath and then the part you don't
say aloud. You do the part you don't say
aloud because that is how you get
engaging content. Right? It is literally
how you get people to engage in your
content. If you can say the quiet part
aloud, I guarantee other people are
going to see it and be like, "Holy cow,
how does he know me so well? Oh my gosh,
he's making me feel seen." That is how
you tend to people through content
alone. That's how you can make one post
and scale your trust to like millions of
people. It's by saying the part you
don't say aloud. And it's going to
require some introspection from you. So
again, the obvious reason, then the
feeling underneath, the part that you
don't say out loud. Let's use an example
for you.
Maybe you drove your kid to school. So I
would literally write the moment I drove
my kid to school. And you're like, but
June, that would definitely not be a
good piece of content. And I would
agree. However, ask yourself why one
time. Well, the obvious reason is I
wanted my kids to be on time. Education
is important. The second why it's the
feeling underneath. The feeling
underneath. Well, I really love being
present with my kid. I love hearing
their life updates. I love the fact that
they have a crush on somebody and I can
hear about it. I love the fact that they
did well in school or I love the fact
that they're trying out for their new
sport team.
Then the part you don't say aloud, you
can ask yourself why one more time. And
this is the real engaging content idea.
I'm finally choosing to be present with
them over work.
Does that make sense? Now, this is a
content that would perform well. This is
an idea that could lead to a brilliant
piece of content. Do you see how you
take a moment, I drove my kid to school,
and you can ask yourself why three times
to understand the part you don't say
aloud? This is the thing that a lot of
parents are struggling with. You would
find your people if you did it this way.
So maybe your moment is I recorded a
video today. Let me ask you why. What is
the obvious reason? Well, I want to grow
a following. Cool. But what is the
feeling underneath? Why?
Well, to be honest, I'm quite scared.
I'll put myself out there and no one
will care. So, this is the whole fear of
judgment, the fear of being seen. That's
real for me. Then tell me the thing that
you wouldn't necessarily say aloud.
Well, even a hundred views means I did
something I was scared to do. So, for
me, I'm realizing impact is really
important. And I'm starting to recognize
this a lot in my life. Like, sometimes
not about the views, it's actually about
realizing that there's other people on
the opposing side of the screen. So,
maybe I want to make a video about never
underestimating the impact our stories
can have even on one person. You can
turn that into a post that looks like
this.
[music]
the one. I made a man so happy when no
little ones. [music] I hope my children
come and visit once or twice a month.
Soon I'll be
the world
of children. [music]
>> Does that make sense? So you take the
raw, you turn into content. Now the goal
is to actually learn how to put that
specifically into a format. Remember,
you do not have to be a natural-born
storyteller. Storytelling is a skill and
you can learn it like any other skill
and it becomes incredibly helpful when
you have templates to learn it from. So
that's why I'm doing this.
Let's introduce what is called the story
arc. Every single story you've ever
consumed whether it was movies, TV
shows, books or plays has three of the
same exact acts.
It has a beginning, a middle and an end.
But the way that I am going to title
this is problem pursuit and payoff. Let
me explain. So to make a video, to make
a story, to make a carousel, to make any
type of post relevant, you need a
problem. Then you need to showcase the
pursuit of overcoming that problem, the
challenges along the way. And then
ultimately, what is the payoff? Was it
successful or was it not?
I call this the 3P framework. It's
problem, pursuit, payoff. And it should
be easy to remember. So now you're being
introduced to another framework. So we
did storytelling wheel. Now we're going
into the three Ps. Another one that
should be quite easy to remember. The
first is problem. It is whatever you as
a person has endured. And then
ultimately the pursuit. How did you
overcome that challenge? And lastly, the
payoff. What was the outcome of that
journey? Anyone in here know the Lion
King?
It's the same thing. It's the Lion King
in Simba's journey. He loses his father
and runs away from his responsibilities
as a king. The pursuit is that he
finally grows up, confronts his path,
and returns to face Scar. And the payoff
is that Simba defeats Scar and accepts
his role as king. What I want you to do
is pay attention to this top right. So,
storytelling usually have themes, but
you're going to see that every single
theme actually has the exact same three
acts: problem, pursuit, payoff.
Anyone in here know Titanic?
The star crossed romance. The problem is
that Jack and Rose come from different
worlds. Rose feels trapped by the life
chosen for her. The pursuit is that they
fall in love and fight against social
expectations. And then the payoff is
that Rose chooses Jack, survives, and
builds a life on her own terms. A
completely different theme, the exact
same three acts.
One more. Anyone in here know to Toy
Story?
Hopefully, you've seen one of these
three.
problem is Woody is afraid Buzz will
replace him.
Pursuit is he tries to get rid of Buzz,
realizes he's made a mistake, and works
with Buzz to get home. The payoff then
is Woody stops seeing Buzz as a
competition and gains a friend. That's a
different theme. Fish out of water. The
honest truth is that once you see it,
you can't unsee it. Like every single
thing that you ever consume that is
remotely interesting has the three acts.
But it's about how do you execute those
three acts? What order do you start to
be a little bit creative with that make
some of the best stories? And that's
what you're going to learn today. You
see, the stories do not have to look the
same. They don't have the same
characters. They don't have the same
themes, but all three Ps will always be
there. And what's beautiful is that
content is the exact same way. So, let
me explain. So, what you're about to see
now are sets of content examples, and
then I'm going to break down each of
them, and then I'll give you the
templates here in a little bit, too.
Let's look at this. So, this is me as a
student, right? So, as a student, I
didn't necessarily have like a big
interesting life, but I'll show you how
I can make an interesting piece of
content. I want to play it and you tell
me if you thought the post was
interesting. Okay?
[music]
>> [music]
>> Okay, let's break this down. First,
what's the problem? [music]
One of 300. So, one of 300 biomemeds and
half of the people have dropped out.
Then the pursuit was me working twice as
hard, which you'll see here. I had no
clue about medicine, but I had to work
twice as hard to build a learning
system,
[music]
but quitting wasn't an option. Then the
payoff is that I was able to graduate
without sacrificing my other interests.
Does that make sense? So, this is like
phase one of what we're going to be
talking about today. I just need you to
build these blocks with me because as I
go into the more advanced things, I
don't want you to get lost. But so far,
does it make sense? So, like I just
said, this is no different from Toy
Story. It's no different from The Lion
King. It's no different from the
Titanic. The best stories have the exact
same three acts. And it doesn't just
work for me. Again, it works for all of
my students. So, Michelle is another
student of mine. I want to play this
video for you. And I want you to think
about, is there a problem? Is there a
pursuit? Is there a payoff? And I am
going to actually do it like this so
that you have full context as you watch
this.
[music]
>> [music]
>> Can anyone resonate with [music]
>> So she's saying the problem is that
there is society's expectation on her
that she doesn't want to follow. Then
the pursuit is actually she writes it in
the caption. So this is where we're
starting to tease a little bit about how
cool these templates can become. Every
single post that has ever performed well
in terms of converting to new followers
always has a problem, pursuit, and
payoff. But the way the order, the
placement of them is the hard part. But
here, pursuit is actually living in the
caption. So, she's talking about it.
She's saying, "Working since I was
seven, no breaks. My 20s were a blur of
multiple jobs. No time to just be me. I
thought once I built something, I'd
actually have time to breathe. And I
did. I found that balance. I'm actually
living now." That's her pursuit. Then
the payoff is what happens after the
music drops.
[music]
>> Does that make sense? So she when she
initially thought about my own teachings
too, she's like, I don't have a story to
tell. I'm like, of course you have a
story to tell. She had to find it
through her storytelling wheel. She
found it and she was able to displace
it. Problem, pursuit, payoff. Cool. This
is like level one. We're going to start
to now add building blocks, but I just
want to make sure that we're all kind of
on the same stratosphere together. I'm
going to really try to grill this home
with something that looks very
different. So, now I'm going to show you
something that is a talking video and
you're going to still see the three Ps
are embedded. This is another student of
mine. Very, very different type of
content, but imagine the three Ps and
why they're there.
>> I was a former college basketball player
and I actually feel more athletic now at
the age of 29. This is exactly what I
did in four simple steps and how you can
do it too as a former athlete looking to
get back into shape. Shoot me a follow
for more content like this. The very
first thing is movement. As we get
older, we simply cannot spend 2 to three
hours like we did back then. So, working
smarter, not harder, is the key to
making consistent progress while only
needing to work out for 45 minutes three
to four times a week. Second, does this
make sense? So, even without me playing
the full thing, you should be picking up
on this right away. So the problem is
this idea of needing mobility and him
losing this as he gets older. The
pursuit then becomes the four methods,
but each time he's embedding his
personal story inside of it. Then the
payoff is obviously that you become more
athletic. Again, building block one. I
just want to show you how this looks
very different for different types of
content, but the three piece are still
embedded. Do not worry. I'm going to
then give you the templates. That's the
fun part. I will make sure that I give
it to you so that you don't have to
overthink it. But I have to give you
baseline value because like if I just
give you the six templates and you can
only do six videos, then obviously
that's not going to give you sustained
success. So now you know why I'm giving
it to you. All right. So can anyone
think about right now why do these three
Ps keep us watching? Why is it that
literally the best directors in the
world and also me as a creator all have
the three Ps? It boils down to human
psychology. Okay? So it's not something
that we're inventing. It's just how
humans function. Why do we lead with a
problem? Let me go the opposite way. You
made a piece of content that was like,
"Man, I'm so handsome. I have a fancy
watch, a lavish vacation behind me, and
I have this beautiful car that I've
always wanted, and I have the most
incredible girlfriend." Like, if you
lead with that type of content, I'm
going to be like, like, no one wants to
watch that type of content. So, our
human common denominator is our
struggle. It's not where we are
currently. It's that we all face
different struggles. We had to no matter
if you are let's say a butician or maybe
you are a movie star. You don't have the
same lives but you've dealt with the
same insecurities. You've dealt with the
same fear of being seen. You've dealt
with imposter syndrome. You've dealt
with guilt. You've dealt with shame.
Like all of those are problems that we
can lead with because that's what makes
people care. If you make somebody care
right away, people stay. They want to
buy into you. They want to see how you
overcome it. So maybe you're thinking to
yourself, "All right, what do I
potentially have as prompts for me?"
Maybe you're not good at something yet.
Maybe you grew up in a disadvantageous
circumstance. Maybe you want to make
your family proud. Maybe you stayed up
all night for a project. Maybe you
messed a painting up and now you're
restarting it from scratch. Maybe you're
an artist. Maybe you're a singer. Maybe
you're a producer. I don't know. But
whatever it is, you just want to start
off with a problem. Small or big, it's
totally fine. It doesn't matter. It's
just that you lead with the problem. Now
that you have resonance, you then go
into pursuit, which is actually your
unique way of solving it. Oh my
goodness. This is how you make a million
dollars. By the way, think about the
pursuit. It is your method. It's your
unique way of solving something. And
that is how you build IP. That is how
people buy into a product of yours. So,
if you think about how I made a million
dollars while still a student is because
I sold something called the guide to
academic success. That was a series of
tips and tools that I've personally used
to become a better student. It was the
pursuit in all of my content. So maybe
you created your own study method like I
did. Maybe you started going to the gym
every day. Maybe you stopped dwelling in
anger and pursued happiness. Maybe you
challenged yourself to post. Whatever it
is, it's fine. It's just your method. So
what is the payoff then? It is the
outcome insight or lesson that you've
learned from that experience. This is
so important. There's always a payoff.
And every time I do this lesson, for
some odd reason, people are like, "But
I've never resolved it." I'm like, "No,
no, no, no. Not having resolved
something is a payoff in and of itself."
Payoff does not mean that you've been
successful. Payoff just means that you
gained a new realization, you gained a
new awareness, or you've taken one step
in the right direction. So even if you
failed or even if it's not fully
resolved, that is the payoff. So for
example, if you had your first day of
college, you're not necessarily going to
make a piece of content like, "So I I
graduated and I had the best grades
ever." No, maybe your first day is like
I feel really unclear with a lot of
things, but at least I went to my class
today. Like that is the payoff. Does
that make sense? And you can speak about
it that way. It's like zooming into that
moment. We're on I would call now like
ground one and a half. So like we
finished level one, now we're going to
like psychology one and a half. Then
we're going to be boiling it into
templates here in a little bit. So here
are some examples of payoffs. Whether
it's you achieving something, maybe it's
you saying, "I literally don't have it
figured out yet, but at least I know
what to do next." It doesn't matter. Any
of these things can be payoffs. It's
just the outcome, insight, or lesson.
So, if you do not have an ARC, you have
no reason to keep watching. So, let me
just quickly go into it like this. If
you've ever looked at your own
analytics, these are called retention
graphs. And basically, retention graphs
literally tell you how long were uh I
would just say your viewers in total,
how long were they retained for on that
post. Aka, if you have a high retention
percentage, it's good. Like, that means
that someone had stayed for a long
period of time. If your retention is
low, you would have something that looks
like this.
you would have a very sharp decline. So
imagine if you actually started off with
the story of I have the coolest watch
ever. I'm the coolest human being ever.
I'm so perfect. I have no insecurity. I
have no flaws in my life. If you did
that, there is nothing to resonate with.
It doesn't feel human. And so
immediately you'll have this sharp
decline. If your content reads like a
list of facts, not a journey, the
viewers will not connect and the viewers
will lose interest as they don't
understand where the content is heading.
So the problem pursuit payoff is to try
and improve this retention graph and it
boils down to that psychology. Add a
story arc and the three Ps do this for
you, right? So the strong hook will give
you much more of this slower gradual
decline and it will start to plateau at
a later state like this. And this is
what having the three Ps do. It makes
your content more engaging. So that was
the promise today that I'm going to help
you deliver and tell stories in a way
that makes it engaging and this is the
high percentage of people watching even
all the way to the end. Okay, so that's
the prom pursuit payoff. So let me show
you some examples of something that has
no arc and then something that actually
has an arc. This is my friend Kadim. He
had joined one of my programs and I'd
helped him. I'm going to play this first
video and I want you to think
why
should he actually try and incorporate
the three PS like ask yourself this
question like does the video feel flat
I just woke up [music] this morning I'm
loaded up the day my mama just want me
to stay out the way I made mistakes as a
young but I had to learn how to watch
what I say I'm with [music] the AP stuff
in the book bag with drip I was just
up looking like anything I got
enough for a
In comparison to something like this,
>> you're spending $200 on one thing for
back to school fit. Do not go back to
school running out of fits first week
because I've been there. When I was in
college, I was spending money on a few
things and I'd be out of fits first
week. So, here's a few places to get
right. I got you. For store one, we're
going with cold culture [music] and
specifically for the hoodies because in
school, me and you both know it doesn't
matter what the weather is.
>> Does that make sense? So, prom pursuit
payoff without having any of that. The
video feels flat. There's no meaning to
the audience. Cool. He got a brand deal,
but why the heck would anyone else care?
How can he start to incorporate brands
though in a way that's interesting,
that's engaging? He leads with the
problem, saying, "Running out of new
outfits for school in the first week."
And he explains that he actually dealt
with the same thing. and because all
these outfits were too expensive. So now
he's recommending affordable places to
shop. So he's taking the same idea, the
same outcome, but he's actually making
it into a story that's engaging. I'll
show you one more quick example. So
let's look at another student of mine,
Janae. And Janae actually has one part
of it, but doesn't have the other two.
She has this slow-mo effect here in the
beginning. So don't be alarmed when it's
a little bit choppy in the beginning.
[music]
Kentucky.
>> This is Jana and it says, "Getting ready
to put get a boyfriend on my vision
board for the third year in a row."
Maybe that's something that you can
attest to, but I would state that the P,
the first P is actually there. The
problem is there. There's a clear
relatable problem. She's never had a
boyfriend. But there is no pursuit.
There is no payoff. So, a lot of your
guys' content lives this way. A lot of
your content actually has no value. Like
it might be interesting, it might be
fun, but it might be meme like, but
there is no value in it. There's no
reason for somebody to come back.
However, let's look at this video. Same
exact idea, but t with the problem
pursuit payoff in mind.
>> I'm 27 and am I alone in this? I've
never had a boyfriend and not even a
situationship. I used to genuinely
wonder if I'm even worth being loved.
But then I realized something that
changed everything. My life wasn't
empty. It was just unassigned. I was
waiting for love from a person to give
me purpose. instead of building a life
that love could walk into, which now
when I say it out loud is kind of
embarrassing, so just pretend I didn't
say that. But I stopped asking myself,
why hasn't he come yet? And started
asking myself, who am I becoming while I
wait? There's purpose in the waiting if
you stop wasting it. Follow me if you're
done wasting your waiting season and
I'll show you what to do with it.
>> Do you understand the difference?
Problem, pursuit, payoff. Exact same
idea, but she didn't actually know how
to give value. Now people are following
her. There's a reason why this has
360,000 views. problem. Never had a
boyfriend. Am I worth being loved?
Pursuit. Looking for purpose in other
places. Payoff, found, purpose, and
waiting. Now, really quick, you can just
take a screenshot of this. I just am
listing to you the common mistakes. When
I think about the three Ps, this is
where most people tend to fall short.
Either the problem is too vague. Like if
you said, "I struggled." That's not
enough. Like, tell me something
specific. Like, what did you actually
struggle with? Payoff. So if you said
something like everything worked out,
you are not going to be rememberable.
Like what is that payoff? Be honest. You
don't have to have it fully figured out.
Maybe you are saying I don't have it
figured out, but that awareness is your
first step. Like that at least gives you
humanity, right? Like you don't want to
just close it off in a generic term. You
want to make it feel specific. And then
finally, a lot of people tend to skip
the pursuit. And that feels more like a
flex than it does actually helpful
content. So if you just have a before
and after with no pursuit there, it just
literally feels like you're just cooler
and better than everyone else. But if
you have the pursuit and you showcase
the journey that you've actually
developed over time, it becomes much
more human, right? It's like not
skipping the middle part. Who is ready
for format number one? So now from this
point forward, I'm going to break down
six of the best performing formats. Now
that you understand the three Ps,
everything's going to fit in those three
categories and it's going to blow your
mind. So, right now, I hope I hope that
you're like a little skeptical because
I'm gonna it's gonna blow you away. It's
gonna completely change the way that you
think of content. You're gonna be like,
"How is he doing this? How has the best
creators in the world that I look up to
actually taking June's work?" Let me
show you. Once you master the three Ps,
you can package them into a format. And
once you have it in a format, it's
actually repeatable. Here we go. So, a
format is literally this. It's just how
you're packaging your information,
right? So now that you have the raw idea
from the storytelling wheel, you need to
know how to package that concept. So it
goes into the world of social media,
right? Are you going to just directly
talk to the camera? Are you going to use
B-roll and tax? Are you going to do a
carousel? It doesn't matter what you
choose. It just means that they have
different purposes. I think the best way
you can think of this is like a topic is
what you're saying. The format is how
you're saying it. It's like packaging
the thing. My most popular format is
called silent film.
So, if you know my content at all, if
you've ever seen any of my posts pinned,
they're always here. And it's something
that I've nailed down and something that
the world is starting to utilize as
well, which is really cool. I want more
people to, right? I I encourage it. So,
I'm going to show you exactly how it
works so you can recreate it. Would you
like that? Would you like a full
breakdown of the thing that got me over
100 million views in like the last year
alone? Just that one format alone? I'm
going to show you step by step how to do
it. Now we're really getting into the
breakings of let's say a specific
format.
Firstly,
I am going to play it and I want you to
think about the prom pursuit payoff that
you might now have in context.
This is the [music] end.
Hold your breath and count
to 10.
Feel [music] the earth move. And then
hear [music] my heart burst
again.
For this is the end.
I [music] drown and dreamed this moment
so overdo I
swept away I'm stoless.
[music]
Let the sky fall
and it crumbles. [music]
Heat. Heat.
>> [music]
>> I love it. I love it. I love it.
[music]
Let's break it down. So, problem that is
set up for the first seven lines of the
video. So, you went through it. It was
that beginning phase all the way up to
here. Sold our childhood home. as I was
embarrassed and I struggled alone. This
then becomes the pursuit, right? So
lines 8 through 15 transitions into what
I did to overcome those challenges.
Okay? And the payoff then is when the
music drops. [music]
>> The three Ps I'm showing you is at the
core of every storytelling post. I am
now going to go more detailed to each
component so that you actually know how
to physically do this. First step,
The problem is visibly done in two ways.
One, you have the text and then two, you
have the photo or you have the video.
And I want to be crystal clear here.
Both have to make sense. They don't have
to actually be in the exact moment,
though. So, the first question that I
always get asked is, "June, I do not
have photos or videos of me when I was
younger." I got you. I want to introduce
you to something called the picture book
effect. If you've ever read a picture
book to, let's say, your child, imagine
how that's constructed. The text is for
you as an adult to read and progress the
story along. The visuals are only there
to amplify the emotion for the kid.
That's what photos and videos do. So,
none of these are actually from 2013.
None of them are actually me upset at
all. This is just me playing a game
called Mafia at a church retreat. So,
this was just me focused. This was
This is me eating an ice cream bar um on
a summer sunny day. Like if you zoomed
out, you would see an ice cream bar in
this hand of mine. And all I'm doing is
I'm just capturing and zooming in and
just showcasing the photo that
represents the emotion.
That's it. And it will change your
perspective on content. So basically all
of my programs, I teach people what are
the emotions that you need to display in
B-roll. And you can film one today and
it'll make the exact same effect. Like
you would never know that you like you
because how in what world would I have
known in 2013 to film content just like
even two weeks ago you might have had a
moment. There's no way that you would
but you don't need it. You just need to
express the emotion with the image.
Another part to this is in the pursuit.
It has to be readable, right? So think
about it like the text is located in the
right place. You can read it. There's
enough contrast between myself and the
text. Then the music was important.
>> Listen to it right here. Up. Up. Up.
[music] up and then down.
>> Okay, cool. Now, let's do a scientific
breakdown of the entire thing. Cool. I I
took photos for you. I'm doing this for
you. And this is like this is like
unreal. This is like like complete. This
there's no one else doing this stuff. I
want to go ahead and give you exactly
how to do this for yourselves. I am
telling you specifically how many lines
are for each problem, seven lines,
pursuit, seven lines, payoff, five
lines. Then I had two and two lines for
reflections and lessons. And lastly, a
call to action. But let me make it even
crystal clear. The number of lines are
not that important. It's just the
amount, let's say, um, of of how the
ratio I don't want to get too
scientific, but do you guys see how the
payoff has five lines here? That's
really all I care to show about. Do you
see the five lines here? Do you see how
the payoff is actually less than problem
and pursuit? That is all I care that you
think about. That's all I'm trying to
show you in this slide. What I mean by
this is that so many of us care to talk
about our successes for like 80% of the
video, but it's actually the opposite.
Problem pursuit should dominate the
video. And it's because that's where
resonance happen. That's where learning
happens. The final outcome should be the
last bit of it. That's all I'm trying to
show you. It's the sequential order
though that makes it all very important.
So think about the viewer here. Like
this is like next level psychology, but
think about it. Like I go into this
video, I see the problem. I resonate.
Then I go to the pursuit that I'm
learning something new. Then I go to the
payoff and I know why I should have
stayed to the end. Does that make sense?
Like I'm showing you the full breakdown
of it right here. Lines means like when
you're actually writing the script,
right? So the the text on screen,
the best creators right now are studying
my formats. The best creators that you
look up to are studying my formats. And
it's an honor. It is the biggest honor.
I I don't have any gatekeeping in mind.
I want people to win. But the worst part
is is that all of these people have like
10 people on their team studying it for
them. You guys don't have that. And
that's why I'm trying to do this lesson
for you so that you don't have to have
team members to go and do all this
research. I can just give it to you.
Okay. I want to show you how really
impressive this is. Anyone know who this
person is? Well, this is interesting.
So, this is a pinned post of his. It's
literally on his pinned Instagram
account to 4.8 million followers. Alex
using that Junior story strategy. Love
it. What a story. Immediately I saw it
and I remembered yours June. Yes, June,
you're the goat. Let's watch it. [music]
>> Hold your breath and count
to [music] 10.
Feel the earth move. And then [music]
hear my heart
again. [music]
For this is the end.
I [music] drown and dreamed this moment.
So overdo [music]
I
swept [music] away and sto
[music]
>> everyone see what is happening. The prom
pursuit and payoff is there. Everyone
see that? And it's the exact same
format,
the exact same thing that people are
taking and implementing their own
respective stories to.
You were seeing something that is
happening in the industry more than
once. Another amazing creator, Shelby.
Let's look at it here. This is [music]
the end.
Hold your breath and count
to 10.
Feel the earth moving. Then [music]
hear my heart burst.
[music]
Let the sky fall
and it crumbles. [music]
We will stand.
Do you see what I'm showing you right
now? I have no problem with this at all.
I actually like the fact that they're
winning. I think there's, this is what I
mean. I think there's place for all of
us to win. The one thing that I'm trying
to do for you guys though is literally
show you I am trying to skip like people
hire fullon teams to study this stuff. I
am literally trying to give to you the
thing and shortcut probably 10 different
hires. Like I'm saving you hundreds of
thousands of dollars. Does that make
sense? what the whole goal of today's
session is. I'm trying to give you the
whole thing that other people are
looking to take from me. I'm just
handing it to you. That's the power of
storytelling content. Are you thinking
that you've learned something new so
far? Are you thinking like, "Holy cow,
this has been value that I've never seen
before. Are you thinking that this is
overly generous? Are you thinking that
because that's not all?" Not only am I
going to give you one, I'm going to give
you five more. Not. So now that you have
proof that literally people like hire
teams to do this, like to study my
formats, I'm going to deliver you five
of my own as well. So now you're going
to have a total of six coming out of
here today completely for free. I want
you to win. I desperately want to see
you win and I want to make sure that you
come out of here and know exactly how to
do it. We're about to introduce five of
the top performing formats today. We're
going to be going over a split screen
reel. We're going to be going advice I
needed at X Age. We're going to be
talking about the old me versus the new
me, the problem statement, and the split
screen carousel. Every single one of
these have been students of mine, and
I'm going to show you how they've done
it physically and how the threepiece
implement into each. So, all you have to
do is embed your story inside of it. Let
me go into the first one called the
split screen reel. So, my head's kind of
covering a little bit of this, so I have
to duck and I'm going to show it to you,
but I had to put it like this so you can
see it in full. Okay? So, I'm going to
play it and I want you to think about
the problem pursuit payoff.
[music]
Where is the problem? Tell me where was
the problem in this content? Cuz now
we're starting to reorganize problem
pursuit payoff. At each frame, the
problem is listed at the top. Where's
the payoff, guys? Where's the payoff? At
the bottom. Nice. Does that make sense?
Like I'm now showing you how the problem
pursuit payoff gets embedded into each
template. All right, let's see if you
can deal with the second one. A little a
little bit a little bit different. Let's
see. Okay, so advice I needed at 22, not
30. This is a carousel. Another student
of mine.
That chapter that you're so afraid of is
actually going to be your favorite.
No is a full sentence. You'll never feel
ready because ready isn't a feeling,
it's a decision. Stop forcing yourself
to be a 6 a.m. girly. The universe
rewards audacity, not potential. Slow
down. Your future is shaped by the
habits you repeat, not the goals you
set. Fill your own cup. Self-care is the
best investment. Practice gratitude. Do
not settle for a dang thing. Where was
the problem in that beginning frame?
Well done right here. So, this is the
problem. She needed these advice earlier
on in her life.
Oh, where's the where's the pursuit? The
in between Tabitha. Come on now. Where's
the payoff? So, the payoff was at the
very very very end. And the CTA as well.
So, let me just go into here. Okay,
cool. So, this and then the the CTA and
the caption. Okay, I'm going to do one
more one. Okay. Or two more ones, I
think. No, three. Three more. Three
more. Old me versus new me. Another
student of mine. Think about the problem
pursuit. Pay off.
[music]
Where's the problem? Yes, at the start.
Where's the payoff? Whoops. I'm showing
you. Nice. And the pursuit here is in
the caption. Nice. I always seeing how
in different formats the prompt,
pursuit, payoff are slightly displayed
separately, like they're different in
each of them. But that's how the formats
work. They're all embedded in there.
These are all of my students. So, I'm
excited that you're starting to
recognize this. Let's look at another
one. Think about where the problem,
pursuit, and payoff would be in this
one.
[music]
[singing]
>> Sailor [music]
taste. Can you tell me what's my flavor?
I don't believe God, but I believe that
you're [singing and music] my savior. My
boss says that she's worried.
>> Where's the problem?
>> The first line. Okay, good. First photo.
Nice. Good job. Where's the pursuit?
Whoops. I keep showing it. Um, in
between. Nice. And the payoff. Good.
Let's look at a split screen carousel.
Oh, I think this is going to need some
time to load, but let me just go into it
like this. Okay, cool. Let's look at
this. A split screen carousel from
Aaron. What's really cool about the
previous examples, too, is that they're
all normal people. You know that one
individual who said the idea of like,
oh, it's just successful people who have
made it. Are you starting to see that
it's like not that case? It's just like
all normal people. But the best creators
are actually developing formats or we're
kind of finding them. And then for all
of us, it's to learn from them, right?
To actually input our own stories to
them.
Let's look at errands here. So it says,
I started saying no and I lost
friendships.
I started sending boundaries and they
stopped counting on me. I stopped
reaching out and no one came to look for
me. I stopped people pleasing and many
walked away. I started respecting myself
and I felt lonely.
Putting yourself first isn't selfish.
It's necessary.
Where's the problem?
Okay, problems at the top. Where's the
payoff?
At the bottom. Where's the pursuit?
And the caption. Look, I said yes to
everyone. my family, my job, my friends,
oldest five that came with the job
description nobody wrote down. I kept
showing up so strong so everyone else
can carry on. Does that make sense? The
prompt pursuit payoff. It's not about
having fancy stories. It's not about
being more impressive than other people.
It's about normal people knowing how to
embed even the smallest moments into the
three Ps and then finally into a format.
And it's like this puzzle matching thing
of like where can it be best optimized
to locate the problem here, the pursuit
and the payoff. So basically what other
people pay tens of thousands of dollars
to hire employees to then go to their
team and get trained upon my content and
my teachings, you guys are getting
completely for free for six of the top
performing formats of 2026. Does that
make sense? Do you see how it's not like
fancy people? It's not like ultra
successful people. Do you see how like
it could be your story inside of these?
Remember we had the storytelling wheel,
the three piece and the formats.
Everyone got that so far? So like we
went over the storytelling wheel, then
we did the three Ps, then we did the
formats. So now I want to go through an
example from the ground up. I want to
show you how this all comes into play.
So let's go. So we have, let's say, a
moment,
and I'm going to choose a moment, and
this is a moment. Let's say I was in
London recently, and I hosted an
in-person mastermind. Basically, I
hosted an inerson event for like 20
people.
Why do I do it? I want to help other
people grow.
But why? What is the feeling underneath?
Well, I want to build something that I
can be proud of. Well, what's the third
why? The raw, the thing that I wouldn't
say aloud. I want to prove that people
like me, immigrant, poor upbringing, can
build something for themselves without
being handed to them. Then the three Ps
give you structure. Then I'm saying,
"All right, people think that immigrants
are stealing their jobs. My pursuit is
that becoming an expert, sharing my
knowledge, hosting events, sharing my
own business, and the payoff is being
able to provide jobs for other people.
So now I'm putting that idea, that raw
idea, and I'm just developing a
three-piece structure that I want. It
doesn't mean that you have to do it this
way, but it's the three piece that is
according to my life. Okay?
Then it turns out to be this.
[music]
>> You
just want to say thank you, Lord. Know
you wonder where the f but I'm back to
life like a pie still [music] in the
leopard skin and check me out then check
me in see this [music]
to my old self wake up to the new me
do you get that like I'm going from the
entire ground up I'm figuring out what
is the storytelling wheel the concept
then I go into the three Ps and I'm
plugging into a format do you get the
whole point of the storytelling
experience and Right now you've been
introduced to again the idea and then
how do we implement within a format.
So we still have a lot more to come.
This was now touching the surface of
like are the information the methods and
then we're going to do audits for people
here in a little bit and we're going to
go ahead and also do a breakdown of some
more good versus bad and we'll do some
Q&A as well. Again I encourage you to
think of it this way. Right now you are
in the backstage. This is how I used to
visualize it growing up. So, I hope that
this analogy makes sense to you.
Thinking, what will my family say about
me? Will everyone judge me? I don't
necessarily want to put myself out
there. I'm afraid of the backlash that I
might receive. But ultimately, we all
want to hopefully be visible. We
hopefully want to do things that are
lying to us. We want to make real impact
and find what we're good at. We want to
have the confidence to speak up. Who in
here wants to feel empowered? Like who
in here wants to feel like okay there is
something in me and I can go and
actually verbalize it and find resonance
right now. How many of you guys have a
voice that's been silenced for years?
How many of you guys have a hidden
story? How many of you guys feel like
the work that you're doing on a daily
basis doesn't fulfill you? It doesn't
feel aligned. Then is this where you
want to be? Who in here wants to be
known for who you actually are and
everything that you've worked hard for?
Who in here wants to create real impact
in other people's lives and finally make
content that you're proud of? You see,
my storytelling frameworks, I just
showed you six of them. You're going to
get a lot more, but my life is too
boring. I wish I knew what part of my
story is worth sharing. I don't know how
to build the right audience. I want to
deliver you from all of these negative
thoughts and insecurities that you have
about yourself. And on the other side, I
actually want you to be where I am in a
place where I can ultimately say that
I've climbed cringe mountain and I can
say the words that I did it right. Be it
let's say it was nerve-wracking. I had a
lot of hesitations. I was very insecure
along the way. But ultimately the
storytelling frameworks make it easy. Do
you believe in the storytelling
frameworks now? Now that I've shown it
to you like directly, do you believe
that there's actual science behind it?
There's actual repeated frameworks
behind it. Do you think you would win
with those frameworks yourself?
Do you think if you had them at your
disposal, it'd be possible? I just want
you to think about are you going to
remain hidden or are you going to become
a storyteller? Truly, I don't mean this
in in a way that feels trivial. Like I
want you to think about it deeply and
take a second to ask, do you want to
stay hidden? It might be 38 years in and
you might be thinking, I don't even
remember the last time I had joy, like
creative work. I don't remember the last
time I actually touched into a passion
of mine. For so long, you have actually
hidden your stories and worries. And
it's actually not even because of your
own fault. A lot of the times it's
because for so long, every time you did
speak up, somebody told you to be quiet.
If you're a storyteller though, can you
show up scared? Can you share what
you're actually good at and find those
things that you're good at along the way
and make people feel something? I was
just in Nice, France. Anyone ever visit
France? Anyone live in France by any
chance? I went there with my girlfriend
and her and I were eating some ice cream
together. It was on July 5th and people
recognized me, which is crazy to think
because France isn't even near the top
locations within my analytics.
We sat there with a lot of people that
recognized not only me, but the work
that I did. So, they knew about Creator
College, my business. And what's the
coolest thing ever is that they were
repeating back to me the stories that I
told online. They were telling the
stories about Creative College, about
how I was able to build this business
from the ground up. They were able to
tell me directly and that was the
coolest thing I've ever been a part of.
So I sat down with them and they were
constantly saying things like, "I can't
wait to save up enough money to join
Creative College." Now to be fully
transparent, my creative college program
has always been several thousands of
dollars because it's been intensive
hands-on. And so they were thinking,
okay, I got to save up for it. And it
made me think like, ah, shoot, maybe
there are people all across the world
that actually really need this stuff
that I'm not able to serve at the
moment. And it was actually in that
conversation that one of them
recommended I do a challenge. It was
them. It wasn't even me. It was them in
conversation like, why can't you just
develop a program that they can do
alongside me and do it in a challenge
format? You see, then I posted on my
Instagram stories like the day of, like
literally it happened. And then I got
onto my phone and started posting
content about it on my stories and I
said, "I need your opinion." Like, if I
ever did something like this, would you
be in? I was telling people that I just
sat down with 50 different people in
France telling me that they knew about
my content, they knew about Creative
College, and they wanted a more
accessible way to do this. And the
answers were an astounding yes. So, what
did I do then? Well, I went on the most
ridiculous sprint that I've been on. And
basically for the last 6 weeks I have
been spending 15 to 18 hours every
single day trying to build something
from the ground up. You see this
challenge never existed before. So I had
to develop an entire curriculum. This is
the curriculum. This is phase one of the
curriculum. Do you see this notebook?
This is literally the first rendition of
the calendar that I posted a story
about. And I asked people, "Do you want
this?" They actually said no for a lot
of the things. I'm like, "Shoot, I got
to go fix it. Let me change it." it. So
this is me doing a second iteration of
it. Then this is me on the whiteboard
doing another iteration of it. And I'm
just like constantly trying to make this
the best thing possible. Now also in the
same breath I have to convince my team
that this is a good idea. At the same
time you can see my wonderful team here
but this was not planned at all within
our year plan at all. So like I'm trying
to convince them this is a good idea.
And at the same time I'm getting
conflict with that. I'm trying to figure
out okay how do I make this work? I'm
asking my people in the audience like
what do we do about this? And I have
such a hard head where I'm like, you
know what? Um, I'm going to make it
happen. So then I got on a call with my
team. I tried to explain to them the
curriculum from the ground up. Started
to convince them. And then my community
made all the big decisions for me.
Literally everything that's part of this
challenge, they did. So I asked them, I
said, "What is the logo that you want?"
I asked them, I was like, "What do you
want in the curriculum?" I said, "Do you
want these videos?" And they're like,
"Yes." I'm like, "All right, let me go
film it." Okay, so do you like this
calendar approach? Great. Let me go film
it. I even did a teased one small part
of the challenge to a 100 random people
within my audience to see if they liked
it. Then I went in and I started doing
like the whole thing was built in
public. I'm going to be fully honest. I
never even wanted to call it the
storytelling content challenge. I
thought it was going to be called the
storytelling sprint. But the audience,
my audience, my community started making
these decisions for me and it was the
coolest experience ever. I wanted to do
it for my community. I wanted to make it
accessible for them. So, of course, I
was going to build it alongside them. We
had this final update here once
everything was solidified. I had the
21-day duration. I had the amount of
classes. I had all of this stuff. And
everyone's like, "All right, cool. We're
in." Like, this is this is the thing
that we wanted. And ultimately, for 38
days, I built this entire thing from
scratch in public. The whole thing. The
whole thing was built entirely in
public. And I got a chance to do it
alongside my incredible community. and
it has turned into one of the most viral
challenges on the internet right now. It
is called the storytelling content
challenge. It has taken the internet by
storm which I could have never imagined
and I want to explain a little bit about
what it is. It is a 21-day posting
challenge. Well, I'll be giving you
these storytelling frameworks and these
templates every single day. So, today I
handed you six, but every single day I'm
going to go focused onto one. So you can
post that video and you can do it
alongside me. I'm going to show you how
I grew 5 million followers and built an
8 figureure business. This is going to
include every single day a lesson where
I'm going to make it very very short. So
it's not going to waste your time. I'm
going to have written prompts that will
help you aid to tailor it towards your
audience. So let's say you're a mom or
let's say you're a fitness coach. Let's
say you're a consultant. Let's say
you're a business owner or a teacher.
I'm going to have like individual
prompts for you so you have many
examples to look at and you're going to
be doing it with a private global
community to keep you accountable and
motivated for the entire 3-week
challenge. So, let me break this down
fully because last weekend I did a
private invite only launch for my
audience who built this with me. Of
course, I did because they're the ones
that had this idea. We did it together.
So, I gave them the first initial chance
of joining. And here's how they made it
the most viral challenge that I've ever
been a part of that I've ever done. And
it's one of the most viral challenges
right now on the internet.
Over 4,000 I think this is closer to
4,200 people now. But over 4,000 people
from all different walks and stages of
life. Like look across here. These are
all very very very different people
saying, "I'm in. I'm so excited. I'm in.
I can't wait to start. I joined. I'm in.
I can't wait to start." There's more.
all these people from all different
walks and stages of life, in different
careers, in different industries, all
committing to telling their stories.
Like, this is crazy. If you go onto my
Instagram, you click into the
storytellers highlight, you're going to
see over 4,000 people that have decided
to say yes to committing to their story.
It's been the coolest thing ever. We
have had over 106 countries, over 106
countries,
every inhabited continent. There's many
people representing each. 106 different
countries have joined the storytelling
content challenge. All united, whether
they're people that are older, whether
there are people that are younger, all
reuniting to be able to say, "I have a
story to tell. I want to find
empowerment in it. Let me go ahead and
do it." Look at this. It's crazy. Like,
what age group do you belong in? We have
all different age groups. We have people
that are doing this for the very first
time at the age of 70. And we have
people that have been a coach for 10
years at 37. And then we have people
that are just coming fresh out of
school. All these different people that
are working together to build again an
incredible community of storytellers.
51 different industries. 51 different
industries. And this was not even
planned. This wasn't even something that
we thought was going to happen. But if
you search up #storytellingcontent
challenge, which we didn't ask any of
them to do this, they have now done this
and now it's like been a thing. And so
now people are making content about the
storytelling content challenge. And now
we have over 4,200 people that are in
this thing with us from all different
walks and stages of life in every single
continent that it's unbelievable.
And I encourage you to watch some of
those contents, too.
So this is what they're going to get. So
this is the 21day journey, the
storytelling content challenge.
Basically, first thing is that you're
going to get immediate access to
something called the toolkit, which has
editing in it, which has idea generation
in it, which has hook development in it.
It has all the basics that you need to
know to be a good creator. However, on
August 22nd and 23rd, we're going to
have two live calls, but they're going
to be recorded. It's going to be at 400
p.m. Eastern on August 22nd, 23rd, but
again, they're going to be recorded. So,
even if you don't make it, you're going
to have immediate access to it. But then
August 24th, the challenge begins. And
every single day, we're going to be
releasing new content every single day,
telling you exactly what to post, how to
do it, like I did for you guys today.
But instead of giving you six at once,
I'll break down one at a time.
Before the posting challenge begins, you
are going to be receiving this first.
Again, those live lessons. In these live
lessons, I'm going to break it down
significantly further, all the different
layers to it. How do you do it for
yourselves? I'll use your guys' content
as examples so it becomes very, very
real for you. This will happen August
22nd and 23rd at 4:00 p.m. Eastern. The
Storytellers toolkit is something else
that you're going to get immediate
access to. And this covers the
fundamentals of everything that you need
to know. So, from let's say how to film
on your phone, like you don't need
anything more than a phone to join, by
the way. That's all you need. So, you
just need your phone and you need a
story. We obviously said that you have a
story. You definitely have a phone, so
you're good to go. I'm going to show you
how to film B-roll and how to build your
own B-roll bank. Then I'm going to
introduce you to many different content
formats. I am going to give you things
around mindsets. So if you're struggling
with, let's say, um, what is the right
perspective on this stuff? How do I make
sure I don't burn out? I cover all of
those things as well. This is going to
be accessible to you for lifetime. It's
available to you for lifetime. So, you
have this, of course, but then you can
have it forever. I'm never going to take
it away from you. This is called the
Storytellers Toolkit, and you get it
immediately upon signing up. Now, once
your 21 days actually begin, this is
what it looks like. You have daily
lessons and prompts. So, every single
day, and I was looking forward to this
slide specifically, but literally every
single day, you will unlock a video, and
the video will actually go over exactly
what to post and why we're doing it. But
if you're extremely busy and you can't
watch this 6 to 10 minute video, I've
done a written form as well, a written
form in summary and I do it templated
for you so you can follow along the
entire way through. So all you have to
do is actually embed your story and
you'll have a post for that day. So the
challenge is through from August 24th
for 21 days and the final day is on
September 13th.
Every single week we focus on a
different type of content. That's going
to be our first step together. So, in
that first week, we're going to be doing
non-talking content, which is all about
basically how do you maximize like this
right sound choice? How do you maximize
the right text? How you going to
maximize the right story line? How do
you make sure that it's engaging to
people? And if you've ever done a
non-talking video, they're much more
consistent to get good viewership if you
do them right. So, this is all about
getting new reach. Like, I'm going to
help you get new reach with seven
content pieces. basically new views, new
followers, and things like that. In week
one, week two, we're going to do talking
videos cuz I'm going to show you how to
deliver a script. I'm going to give you
a script per day. I'm going to actually
tell you exactly how to deliver it. I'm
going to show you how to edit it. I'm
going to show you exactly the music that
you need in it, every single bit of it.
All you have to do is embed your own
respective story, but I'm going to
prompt it out for you. So, you just have
to fill in some answers. Then, the third
week, we're going to be going over
carousels. So carousels are those
pictures that we basically swipe
through. And this is going to be the
final format, but it's one of the most
powerful formats today. And I have a
partner at Instagram and she has always
said in the past year at least that
carousels will continuously keep getting
new reach. And that's going to be a new
format for many of you to try and break
down exactly how to do that as well. Not
only that, you're going to get some
community and accountability. So, inside
of this challenge, you're going to get
many different things, but one of the
most important is that you're actually
going to have people around you like
this that are doing the challenge
alongside you. So, that is me. And this
is a completely private community. And
you're going to have an opportunity to
make sure that you have new friends, to
make sure that you have people that
support you. Like, I think a really good
way of putting this is how many of you
guys have literally zero creator friends
like local to you? like you don't have
anyone that would understand what you're
trying to do here. You would be looked
quite foreign for even trying this.
Imagine you got 50 new followers and
those 50 new followers are all part of
the challenge who are doing the exact
same thing as you and immediately in
your comments you had 50 positive
comments of people saying they support
you, they encourage you. That's what the
challenge can actually deliver to you.
The 21-day journey in a quick summary
point looks like this. Immediately,
you're going to get access to the
toolkit. Then you're gonna get the two
live calls. Then the challenge will
begin for three weeks. And every single
week will be focused on a different type
of content. At the very end, I'll also
give out prizes, too. So, you'll walk
away with not just theory, but 21 real
pieces of content that help tell your
story, share your skills and expertise,
and allow you to make content that feels
makes you feel very confident. But
because you're here with us and because
you've been with me for the last 2
hours, I want to do something special
for you. I want to give you three
content fundamental resources as
bonuses. The first one is called the
unscrollable first post. I'm actually
going to break down the most viral
formats today of August 2026 in written
form. So, this is something you can
actually print out if you'd like. And
this will allow you to give your first
introductory post. You can actually even
pin this post if you want as well. It's
going to get you started on the right
foot.
The second is going to be the silent
film storytelling playbook. The silent
film storytelling playbook is basically
the thing that you just saw with that
Skyfall video, but I'm going to break
down every bit of detail and deliver
upon how you would do it per your own
experience and background. So, I have
some written prompts for you to fill out
as well, and I'm going to show you
exactly how I've done that video that
has got me 100 million views across all
of my posts.
Both of these are normally worth $596,
but I'm going to give both to these for
free. And this third one that I really
like is called the Viral Vault for
Storytelling, where I'm going to do a
full breakdown of my top five personal
favorites that have converted into the
most amount of followers for me. And so,
basically, I'm going to show you all of
my like previous posts that have
converted into the most new followers.
So, I'm going to show you what are the
highest converting posts today and break
down break them down exactly so you can
fill them out for yourselves. normally
$596 as well and you would get them for
free. So all three of them are $596
individually and I'm going to package
all that completely for free for joining
today.
Not only that, I'm going to give you a
fourth bonus called stories that sell.
This will be a free bonus lesson with me
on how to turn story-led content into
actual revenue without ever sounding
like a sales pitch. So I'm going to show
you then how these stories actually turn
into a product. How do you develop IP?
How do you ultimately sell something?
And this is a completely free bonus for
you as well, which is normally worth
$596.
And I'm going to do it in a recorded
fashion so that you don't have to attend
live. You can do it if you're extremely
busy. You'll still have that resource
for lifetime, too.
So, looking at those bonuses alone, each
one of them being $596,
you're going to get those for free. But
let's actually see the amount of value
that you're about to receive.
By the way, all of these are lifetime
access. I'll never strip them for you.
You can have them forever. I want to
talk about the core challenge, which
includes one live lesson with me on the
storytelling framework, normally worth
$1,999.
Then you have another live lesson with
me on storytelling arcs, which is
normally worth $1,999.
Then you have 21 daily teachings and
tactics on what to post, normally worth
$596. You have the storytellers toolkit,
normally worth $596.
You have the private community and daily
accountability, normally worth $996.
And you have lifetime access to every
single bit of this. Every single bit of
it. Every single bit of it, which would
also be worth $996.
So the total value of the challenge, the
total value of all of this is $9,566.
But I'm also going to throw in something
called the AI storytelling coach. I have
three pages and all of them include
prompts. And basically, you're going to
paste this into claw and it'll become
your new storytelling coach. But you
see, AI should never write your stories
for you because the moment it does, it
stops becoming yours. What it will do,
however, is help you find them. It's
going to go from safe to real to raw.
It's going to help you actually turn
that into three Ps and then ultimately a
script that you can deliver upon. So,
it's still your story, but you're using
this prompt to help you with it. And
this is normally worth $596 and you'll
receive it completely for free. So then
if we stack that as well, then that 596
puts the total at $10,162
worth of value.
One more thing though, I want to give
you
the most valuable and exclusive lifetime
playbook from me that has always been
reserved for my one-on-one clients, but
you guys are actually going to receive
it for joining the storytelling content
challenge. And if you had joined before,
I am going to give it to you as well.
So, don't worry. Everyone that has
joined already, I will definitely give
this to you uh because this is
unbelievable.
Basically, everything that I'm about to
teach you within the challenge, I will
actually do it in written form as well
that has space for you to write out
answers to prompts that you can then
deliver into content. So, this becomes
your playbook that follows along every
single lesson, every single video, so
you know exactly how to do it. So, this
is what it's going to look like. So,
you're going to have things that ask you
questions between safe, real, raw.
You're going to be able to fill it in
for each of your ideas. You're going to
have content examples that are broken
down. You're going to also have the
storytelling wheel and tell you exactly
how to apply it for yourself. We're
going to also give you space to write
notes throughout the process. So, this
playbook of yours becomes the holy grail
so that you know exactly what to do and
you never miss out on a single bit of
detail. This again is normally reserved
for my one-on-one clients and it goes
for $5,449
and I'm actually going to add this to
the storytelling content challenge
completely for free. So, that's like a
no-brainer. Okay, that's like the cherry
on top. The thing that I think will
absolutely blow you away. So, the total
value of this challenge comes out to be
$15,661.
The total value of this challenge comes
out to be $15,661.
But you're not paying $15,661.
You see, the public price, the full
price starting on August 21st will
actually be $549.
However, if you do decide to join us
today, you'll receive even $200 off of
that and only need to pay $349
for all of this. For everything that
I've now just mentioned, you can get for
just $349.
That's it. $349 and you'll get access to
all of it.
There's also a chance to win $8,499
worth of prizes at the end of the 21
days.
So, in summary, the two live lessons
with me, the 21 days of daily drops,
daily teachings, which are recorded. If
you miss any of the dates, it's totally
fine. You can pick up on where you last
left off. You can do this at your own
pace. 100% fine. The 21 days of daily
teachings,
the storytellers toolkit,
which breaks down editing formats,
hooks, and more. The three content
guides, the unscrollable first post, the
silent film storytelling playbook, and
the viral vault. The private community,
the AI storytelling coach, the stories
that sell, the prizes worth $8,499,
and the ultimate content playbook.
you'll receive not for $15,661,
but just $349
if you invest today. That's it. You get
access to all of this for just $349 if
you invest today. The cool part about
this is we actually have done this in a
way that's not going to overwhelm you.
There's a lot coming your way, but the
best part is the first thing that you'll
unlock is going to be called the
toolkit. So you'll have access to that
and then on August 22nd everything else
will unlock for you. So all things will
unlock as the challenge ensues so that
you're not like fully overwhelmed with
everything. But basically you're going
to get all of it but you'll get it
alongside us in real time so that you
know how to actually use it.
Plus lifetime access to all lessons,
prompts, resources, and recordings so
you can restart your own 21 days
whenever you want. So, even if you're
extremely busy and you think, "Oh, but
I'm not going to be able to make it
because of a trip or something like that
or because I'm going to be busy for this
season or because of work." You can join
right now, you're going to get access to
all of this. It's meant for busy people
and you can take it at your own pace.
So, if you miss a few days, if you miss
week one, Thursday through Sunday, there
is no penalty. You just come back and
you pick up on where you last left off
and you'll have this material forever.
So, you can keep restarting your 21 days
whenever you want. So, coming out of
this, you're going to feel incredibly
confident. You're going to have
literally 21 posts where you don't have
to overthink a single thing. You don't
have to overthink at all a bit of it at
all. And you just go ahead. You know
exactly what to post. And ultimately,
you're going to be doing it alongside me
and incredible community together, too.
So, if you want the core challenge with
the two live lessons, the 21 days of
teaching, the private community, the
storytellers toolkit, the bonuses, the
three content guides, the stories that
sell, the storyteller AI coach, the
anatomy of a scroll stopping hook master
class, you're going to receive that for
$349.
You can have the QR code here. This is
the opportunity. Like everything that
I've been conjuring up is is right here
in front of you. Everything, right?
Everything from having your voice be
hidden, from everything about constantly
being told not to speak up for yourself,
every single time that you have actually
hidden your real desires. It's like the
thing that you have inside of you that
you can tap into. I'm telling you, you
don't have to wait to be somebody. You
already have those lived experiences and
that is the asset. Now, that's your job
to come and show up. I can help you
extrapolate that into story posts every
single day. You're going to post it, be
proud of it, feel aligned to it, and
think about everything that ensues after
this. One, you're going to have 21
posts, but two, you're going to finally
understand a method that works for you.
It's not about like, oh, you should
teach this topic when it has nothing to
do with you. It's not about niching
down. It's not about going ahead and
choosing an industry. It's not about
using specific hashtags. It's like you
you don't even have to be an incredible
editor. I will literally walk you
through how you can do this just on your
phone and just showing up. You will have
those templates to utilize. And I think
that there is nothing better than
putting your story out there, finding
your own community, and finding
confidence in that. This is the real
impact that we ultimately want to have.
I've also done something where you can
actually do a payment plan if you would
like to. And so you could do $199 by
two. And so that just means basically
you'll pay $199 today. You'll get access
to the storytelling content challenge
and the second payment of $199 will be
due on August 20th. That's it. So if you
want to join today, you can join for as
low as $199.
Another attempt to make this as
accessible as possible for you.
That means again you can join us right
here with this QR code. This is your
chance to join us within the
storytelling content challenge. And I
think we're going to have an incredible,
incredible time together. So, you're
gonna have the core challenge, the
bonuses, the exclusive perks. Again, not
for the $15,661
of value, but 96% off and all you have
to do is pay $349 or do the installment
plan and join us for as low as $199.
If you're ready to join, again, I hope
that you are. And I want to do one more
thing. I'm actually going to offer a
100% money back guarantee. 100%. I'm
promising you because if you think about
it, right, the whole thing of this has
been to find your tribe, to find your
community. It's not about going viral,
but it's about finding your first 100
people, your first 500 people, your
first a,000, your first 5,000, your
first 10,000. You see, I am guaranteeing
you in total over 21 days, you will have
10,000 views. Within those 21 days, you
will get 10,000 views. That means 10,000
people all across the world will know
your story, will actually find rapport
and trust and connection with you, and
you'll have that impact that you've
always desired. There's no way that
you're going to be able to do that in
your day-to-day lives. It's through
content and being able to scale that
trust with just one post.
If you don't get 10,000 views in the 21
days, I'll return 100% of your
investment.
Every single dollar, I'll return. This
is how it works. All you have to do is
just show up. So, you show up, do the 21
days, the 21 posts as instructed by me
in the daily drops. You're gonna follow
the lessons. You're going to watch them
and show up daily all the way till um
the end of the challenge. You're going
to share your content on Instagram with
the challenge hashtag and you're going
to show up in the community for your
fellow storytellers throughout the
challenge. That's it. If you do that, I
guarantee you'll find that impact. I
guarantee you'll find your tribe. I
guarantee that you're going to have
10,000 views in total across the 21
days.
This is who's already within the
storytelling content challenge.
The storytelling content challenge is
officially here and this is how many
people signed up. My name is Abacus
Finch.
>> I'm Tracy. My name is Kyle.
>> My name is Eddie.
>> I'm Janine.
>> My name is Amy.
>> My name is Randy. [music]
>> I've joined the 21-day storytelling
content challenge with Junu and Creator
College.
>> About 15 months ago, this creator, Junu,
created this thing called [music]
Creator College.
>> And the Creator College team is running
a 21-day challenge to tell your story. I
could not have hit that purchase button
fast enough. [music] I'm joining this
challenge with Junu and Career College.
I have a story to tell that is still
teaching me something. I just joined
June's storytelling [music] challenge.
I've decided to spend the next 21 days
telling the story I've spent years
trying not to tell.
>> Already see amazing [music] results in
my mindset in how I plan content in how
I see content.
>> My life was like really [music] really
boring. I realized that I really really
want to grow as a content creator.
>> I joined the storytelling challenge to
get [music] better at sharing my
journey. I want to learn how to tell the
story of my 50 plus years in a way that
helps women. [music]
>> I have so many stories to share.
>> We can always use a refresher, learning
new skills, learning new formats.
>> I'm an amunition to [music] master
storytelling my content. Through this
journey, I've learned tools to help me
get unstuck. Perspective shifts that
help me get going again.
>> And I joined June Storytelling Challenge
because I'm in the middle of rebuilding
my life.
>> Now I'm rebuilding my life as a [music]
mom of two whilst building my dream
beauty brand. connect with other
creators who are pushing their
boundaries and to keep my own momentum
and energy up.
>> What I want to do is master story style
[music] reels.
>> I discovered that I had lost the most
important person in my life, myself.
>> I want to dive deep into storytelling.
>> I joined this challenge [music] to
become a more effective communicator.
>> People follow people met a niche.
>> I think stories are how we [music]
learn. That's how I learn. I just want
to use this opportunity to improve my
storytelling since I've been struggling
for years to just post consistently
[music] and putting myself out there.
>> Now I want to learn the right techniques
to make my stories more authentic,
relatable, and inspiring [music] for the
others.
>> I've posted every day for the past 334
days. I could post again 21 days in a
row with this guy's help.
>> I'm so excited to be [music] back. I'm
so excited to see what they have to
teach us now.
>> I'm really excited. This was a little
thing I did for myself and um [music] I
can't wait to work with June and his
team again. Every single one of these
people, these beautiful faces,
are all very different. Some of these
people have never taken a chance on
themselves. Some of them are 50 years
old and older. Some of these folks are
30 years old becoming a coach for the
very first time. Some of these people
are new parents. Some of these people
are just lost in life and have no idea
what to do with their content. Some of
these people have never ever shared
their stories and now they're joining
this challenge and actually taking that
first step. And it's the coolest thing
because when these people come together,
they find home, they find community.
Like that's the thing that we're trying
to build here. Like all of these people
who come from complete different
backgrounds, how the heck are they
reuniting? How can somebody in all these
different continents come together and
actually do the same thing? It's because
we're all connected through stories.
Like every single one of these people
are going to inspire me. Every single
one of these people that are going to do
the challenge are going to inspire you.
And that's the beauty behind this. Like
I encourage you if right now you're on
the fence of joining the storytelling
content challenge. I want you to think
about those voices inside of your head.
What doubt is it in your brain and think
about how much of that is actually
boiled into reality. Imagine how much of
that goes away immediately when you get
clarity around exactly what to post and
how to show up. Imagine what it looks
like when you have an entire community
supporting you. Imagine what it looks
like when you join, you get immediately
100 new followers from people that are
supporting you. Imagine having that
support. Imagine having that
accountability. Imagine this idea that
every single day we're going to be on
calls together. If you want to be and
you can go ahead and learn from one
another. You can ask questions. If
someone else wins, imagine the
opportunity to be like, "Wait, how did
you do that?" And this person not being
like, "Oh, no, no, don't ask me a
question." But being like, "Yeah, here
you go. Like, go and do this thing." For
a lot of us, we have never been in a
spot where we have a community to
actually do this stuff with. And that
gives us all these voices in our head
saying that it's not good enough, that
we're not good enough. And this is what
I'm trying to deliver you out of. And
that's what the storytelling content
challenge is all about. Like this whole
thing is quite intimate for me. This
whole thing is quite personal because
ultimately I've had this dream of always
developing a safe place for my audience
to be themselves. And I think we've done
it here with the storytelling content
challenge. I'm being told that now we
have wellclipsed over 4,400 of you guys
in it and I just can't wait to see more
of you guys uh partake within this
challenge together. It's going to be a
lot of fun. Let me go through a few of
your questions. You're promising money
back. Will I actually see views on my
own page? Let me go through it. So,
first we have the wonderful Anna. So,
Anna is a student who grew 4,000
followers with only two reels as a
beginner creator. that we have someone
like Charlie who has actually grown
64,000 followers in just two months. And
then we had someone like Lucy, an artist
and painter who gained 800 followers
from a single talking head reel. Then we
have Brian, a dad who reached 871,000
views on a non-talking storytelling
piece of content. This could be you. All
normal people, all not people that have
tremendous successes in their lives, but
people that have been willing to share
their stories and they've got an
opportunity to do that with the right
formats. I've never talked on camera.
Will it work for me? Of course. Anna, a
cancer researcher who is literally at
Oxford right now and spends majority of
her time within a lab got 10 million
views with a talking head video. Or
someone like who got 93,000 views by
talking about his journey. Or someone
like Nelly, a foodie and travel
enthusiast who got 3.6 million views. We
have Bri, a business coach who generated
over 1 and a half million views. We have
Dr. Christine who had multiple viral
videos. And then we also have Charlie, a
tech employee who started with 167
followers and now has 65,000 followers.
Like like look at all the differences in
backgrounds. All people who had no
confidence showing up online, learned
that their stories were important,
stopped trying to be somebody else, and
then ultimately learned how to build
their own respective communities. Now
they have that impact. Have you ever
thought that you don't ever want to do
this alone? Have you ever thought to
yourself that there's no one around you
that understands what is it that you
want out of life? Nobody who actually
wants to take a chance on yourself?
Nobody that seemingly believes in you?
Maybe even the people closest to you are
the ones that aren't supporting you.
Maybe the people like your family, like
your friends are the people that look at
you and you're worried about the passive
aggressive statements and are going to
think that you're doing something that's
not serious enough. If you have ever
worried about how will I get the
attention, the right attention, this is
how what we're going to have within the
storytelling content challenge is an
accountability partner. And if you elect
to, you can enter. You can join. And we
have people that, let's say, are joining
based on location. We have people in
Australia, for example. We have people
that are sharing similar goals, similar
age groups, or people that want to
support one another. We have advanced
creators going with more beginner
creators. like you can find all these
respective people and there's space for
you to find literally one person that's
going to go ahead and show up with you
every single day and you're going to
have these live calls that you can enter
and do this alongside. So you can go
ahead and join this it'll look like this
and basically if you look at my screen
you'll see the hangout call. Every
single one of these are people that are
joining calls that are just with each
other every single day just working
together being accountable with one
another. Uh that's the type of community
that you're going to be a part of. you
get support from people on the exact
same journey as you. So, if you're
struggling, right, maybe you don't have
something to post that day, maybe you're
not inspired that day, you have an
opportunity to learn from somebody and
go ahead and say, "Here we go." Like,
like you have an idea like, "Let me hear
it from you. Let me go ahead and back
and forth with you. What do you think
about this idea? Oh, you do like this or
let me try it this way." You get to work
with one another and bounce these ideas
from people that might be on the exact
same stage as you, people that are a bit
more advanced than you, um, with a lot
of learning opportunity. and you can
finally be in the right room.
This all of this, the two live lessons,
the 21 daily teachings, the storytellers
toolkit, the private community, the
content guides, the ultimate content
playbook, the AI storytelling coach, the
stories that sell all of this and worth
up to $10,758.
You can receive for a fraction of that,
just $349. And you'll join that. You can
join all of us at the storytelling
content challenge.
>> [sighs and gasps]
>> If you think right now that no one wants
to hear your story and you're like, "Ah,
are people actually going to care about
this?" Every single one of these people
that I'm about to show you have the
exact same fear. You see, this fear of
being seen, the fear of being cringed,
the fear of being visible is not
inherently unique to you. It's actually
the badge that you got to wear to get
into this world of social media because
we're so in our own heads all the time.
We overthink about everything. So Nicole
came in had the same exact fear she
learned and this was a student of mine
and now she was able to get 3 million
views. Jake and Shay who shared their
life stories and got 600,000 views as a
couple. Caven who was talking about
basketballled content and he had just 55
followers. He didn't want to show up at
long line. He didn't even want to show
his face at all but he did. He showed up
and he got 300,000 view reels. He's
talking about his perspective, his story
as he's becoming a basketball player. Or
Boxy, who had been burnt out for a long
time, reached 3 million views and gained
2.4,000 followers with this post again.
So, if you're somebody that has ever
tried content before, maybe you've even
tried other courses before. Like, this
is going to be completely different.
This is not a course. This is for you
every single day. Know exactly what to
post. I'm going to teach you the
fundamentals to ensure that you know how
to edit on your phone, that you know how
to capture footage, and you can turn out
to be exactly like my students, right?
You can actually start to get your first
wins, find that love once again for the
work that you used to enjoy. We had
Nicole who had viral talking videos and
she had like literally zero posts
beforehand. She starts talking about
parenting cuz that's what excites her in
her life at the moment. She had done
that and she ultimately started getting
hundreds of thousands of new views,
thousands of new followers on a weekly
basis. That's what happens when you
think you have a boring story, but you
learn the exact right way to tell it and
then you find your people and that's
ultimately how you grow the right
audience. Like that's the whole entire
goal. Abanel, another mom here, got
multiple viral videos sharing her story
and she only had 3.8,000 followers to
start with and ultimately left with
thousands of new people. If you think
your industry is too niche and will it
work for you? Absolutely. Right. We had
Uni, a nursing student who started a
brand new page, posted a talking head
reel about her story and gained her
7,000 new followers overnight. 7,000 new
followers overnight just starting as a
student. She started a brand new
account. Or someone like Arpatha, a chef
who gained a,000 followers with a single
post by sharing her story. or Rich and
Debbie, parents who grew 4 and a half
thousand followers with just 10 posts.
Or Lucky a DJ who grew 400 followers
with a single talking head reel in 24
hours. Like all people that thought
there's no way that people are going to
be caring about the job that I do, about
the work that I do and was able to find
their stories in it and then ultimately
develop businesses behind it, right?
Find new clients for it, find new people
to coach, find new potential people to
sign up for their events and things of
that nature. So again, you can join us
within the storytelling content
challenge. This is it. Like I don't know
how to overly express this, but
this is going to be the coolest thing
that I've ever done in my entire life. I
I don't mean to be dramatic about this,
but the storytelling content challenge
is basically the mirage of all of my
experiences and skills. And for the
first time, these teachings are becoming
accessible to all of you. For the very
first time, I'm coming out with a
program that isn't thousands of dollars,
but 349, an opportunity for you to
learn. It's the very first time that I'm
developing something that I'm actually
doing alongside you publicly. It's for
the very first time I'm actually
developing the community that I've ever
that you know, you know what I can even
show you? Like I had done this
and this wall
that wall
is literally
every single person that has joined the
storytelling content challenge. Like, if
you don't believe that this is personal,
if you don't believe that this is about
to be the best experience that you've
ever had, this is my office space. Like,
every single day I am putting up new
names on here. Every single day I come
in here and I do another post note and I
put a name of a person. Every single day
we have people from all across the
world. Benjamin Puit, Lola. We have
people like Bernal. We have people like
Jenny and Kim. We have people that are
doing couples accounts, creating content
about their training journeys. We have
people that are talking about their
businesses, trying to get more clients,
being able to tell their stories,
respectively, starting to actually
develop a personal brand for the first
time and not a business theme page. For
the very first time, these folks are
doing something for themselves. And I
think it's the coolest thing that I've
ever been a part of. If you're somebody
that's being in this this state where
you don't necessarily think it is for
you, I want you to think again. Every
single one of them had the exact same
thoughts like, "Oh, I don't want to be
seen. Oh, I don't want to be visible.
I'm worried about what my friends are
going to think about me." People have
said that I could potentially do content
before in my past, but then I never
actually took the chance on it. Now I
feel like I'm behind. Like all of these
people have gone through the exact same
thing as you. People that are 6 years
old, people that are 23 years old,
people that are 37. And ultimately us
together are doing this challenge. And
this this is what it's all about. Like
every single day having an opportunity
to work alongside you and make sure that
you feel seen, make sure that you have
a story to be told is the goal here. And
I hope I hope that you find your own
respective voice. I hope that you
actually understand that this isn't just
meant this is not like a gift. It's not
that the most elite, the most talented,
the most successful people have this
opportunity. It's at your disposal on
this phone of yours. You get a chance to
actually join the storytelling content
challenge and build something that
you're proud of. And I hope I really
hope I really hope that you decide to go
ahead and take a chance on yourself. I
want to go through some questions that I
know that you guys have and break this
down further for you.
Many of you guys think your life is too
boring. Many of you guys think that you
live too much of a mundane ordinary life
and many of you guys are starting from
complete zero. Let me address this head
on. What you think is boring is because
it's become a routine. It's become
something that you do on a regular
basis. But that also means that you
could throw a rock and hit somebody in
your vicinity that is also doing the
same things that are experiencing the
same things. But it's up to you then to
cultivate meaning out of it. So, it's
not about living a more special life.
It's not about traveling more or making
more money. It's not about having a
cooler job or a fancier car. It's not
about waiting to get the promotion and
then making contact. It's about having
your boring quote unquote life, your
ordinary life, and finding meaning in
the smallest moments. Finding meaning in
the things you love. Finding meaning in
your culture. Finding meaning in your
age, your wisdom, finding meaning in
what you do as a working professional,
what you find meaning in in terms of
your family, like finding meaning in
your own so-called and whatever goal you
ultimately have for this, right? It's
about finding meaning in those things.
Now, for you, lucky for you, I'm going
to help you find that meaning, right?
So, I'm going to work alongside you to
make sure you're extracting it, put in
the right formats that ultimately you
can grow with it. So, this is meant for
people also that are from pure pure
ground zero. Like, if you've never
posted a piece of content, this is for
you. If you've never edited a piece of
content, I literally sit there, right?
Like, when I say that I built it for
you, I mean it. I sit there editing a
piece of content from scratch, showing
you the entire tutorial, like on my
phone on literal Cap Cut. I just screen
record and I show you the entire thing
of how I edit a video so that you don't
have to overthink it. I show you where I
get B-roll, how I film it, and all
things like that. Every bit of it.
That's the whole goal of the
storytelling content challenge. If
you're from the pure ground zero, do not
worry. I'll help you do it. And I
promise you, you do not need a success
story. In fact, content that's in the
journey perspective, someone that's
trying to reach a new success or a new
goal, even that is incredibly powerful
content. I'm going to show you exactly
how to do it. Like, don't wait because
if you make it now, one, you do it the
right way. Don't wait. Cuz if you go
ahead and you do this and you try
learning from all the free information
online, all the things that tend to be
like it's crazy because you'll hear from
somebody on one topic, another person
that you scroll will say the exact same
thing in a different way and you're
like, "Wait, do they agree with each
other or do they disagree with each
other?" It becomes overwhelming. You can
build it the right way from the ground
up. You don't have to waste any time.
You don't have to waste any effort. And
I really do think that you would benefit
at pure zero, growing an audience that's
fully aligned to you. I think telling
your story is the easiest way to grow
10,000 followers. I think telling your
story is the easiest way to find
resonance with your audience and to
build a community that you really enjoy.
So, absolutely. What help do we get on
what to post? Every single day, I will
do the whole thing that we did today,
which is like a template. I'll show you
exactly how to place your story in it.
Then, I have written prompts to help
discover based on who you are, your
background, and your audience, and who
you want to serve exactly what you
should make that day. like scripts,
[laughter]
formats, templates, every bit of it is
going to be handed to you. All you have
to do is be willing to embed your story
inside of it. And then we're going to be
doing it together. So, of course, if
you're afraid, you're going to have your
accountability partner to to hold you
and to make sure that all of you have a
successful process. So, absolutely, this
is for you. Which one to post from?
Should I post on my personal account or
my business account? Here, we're talking
about personal brands. So, I'm not
talking about a business page at all
here. So, in fact, I would encourage you
to start a personal page and it's
because people buy into people. Even if
you think about my business, right? Was
it the Creator Colleg's Instagram or was
it my personal brand that got people to
join the storytelling content challenge?
It's my page. It's my association. My
business page is meant for testimonials.
It's meant to disclose new updates, new
features. But my personal brand is the
thing that drives traffic to my business
page. So, if right now you're just doing
a business page, the reason why you're
not growing, it's not because you suck
at content. It's because you're making
the wrong thing. If you built a personal
brand and then funneled the traffic into
your business page, both of them would
grow. So, if you don't even have a
personal account yet, you'll make one.
You're going to make one from day one
and you're going to have the opportunity
to build this from scratch. So, you're
going to be totally fine. How will
three-piece work for a product on my
page? So, ultimately, what you're going
to do is based on what it is that you're
selling. Let's say that you're selling a
wedding service and you're a wedding
planner. What you're going to do is you
can tell stories about one, why you
decided to become a wedding planner.
Two, tell stories about potentially the
work you did for your clients. The way
you talk about your actual process
behind the work, like why you make
certain decisions, why do you have these
steps and protocols in your entire
service package? That why is the thing
that's going to make people buy into
you? And I'm going to help you do that.
So that's the thing that's ultimately
going to sell. So, like for example, if
I searched up wedding planner on
Instagram, I'm going to see 250 wedding
planners in my local region. Why the
heck would I choose you? However, if I
saw your perspective, if I saw your
opinion, if I saw your method, if I
understood your background, you
immediately become someone I want to
work with. I want to give you money. And
so, that's the whole idea. You're going
to be doing this underneath your
personal name on a personal brand. If
you have to start a new account, that's
totally fine as well. And I think it's
important to recognize that there is no
better way to have top offunnel
attention. Like you business owners are
so good at bottom offunnel stuff. You're
so good at positioning yourself. You're
so good at being able to convert people.
But right now you have like 3,000
followers, right? Like you have no you
don't have attention. You have maybe
12,000 followers and barely any
engagement on your post. But if you did
the personal branding through
storytelling, if you got people to buy
into you, people can see themselves in
your experience, why you became a
wedding designer, why you became a real
estate agent, why you became a coach,
why you did these certain things. People
start to understand the inner workings
of how you operate and people want to
buy into you. Storytelling has been
around for I mean generations. Like
think about Coca-Cola, think about Nike.
What is the feeling or impression that
you get out of it? And they use people
representatives to actually go ahead and
disclose that. You get to do that for
your own businesses and your own
services. So personal branding like Alex
Shamozi, there's a reason why he does
the content that he does. There's a
reason why Shelby Sap does the content
that she does. There's a reason why all
of your favorite people that have
businesses do the same things. I just
sat down with the co- founder of Mind
Valley, if you know Mind Valley, and we
sat down because he was on my podcast
and it was him talking about how if you
don't build a personal brand today as a
business owner, like you'll never make
it. Because the honest truth is that
there's too much competition. There's
too much saturation. The only way to
stand out is to be human. While
everything else in our world right now
is going antihuman and becoming more
AIdriven, if you can become human, you
immediately separate yourself from a
crowded feed. And so he's talking about
as a Mind Valley founder, right?
Somebody that is in charge of hundreds
of millions of dollars. When he shows up
in the content, everything about his
business, conversion rates go up.
Everything. Even email open rates go up.
even um ad conversions go up. Everything
you can imagine, content engagement goes
up because he's the founder and people
buy into people and that's what you
should be doing on your own personal
branding page. You can start a
completely new account. That's totally
fine and ultimately you can build it
from scratch with us. We obviously still
have a lot more to come with the good
versus bad storytelling content and more
Q&A. I want to talk about this question
as well. Will this challenge help you
get more clients and make more money?
And I want to really drive this home
because now I can show you real proof of
this. Erica, a coach who was not getting
clients by the way. She had actually
been plateaued and losing followers
through storytelling. She grew her
audience another 10,000 followers and
got 10 paid high ticket coaching clients
through her content just organically,
pure organic. Why? Because once she
started telling her story of why she
became a Latina coach and speaker, all
of a sudden people started to buy into
her. And therefore, when she started to
sell things, people like, "Oh, I want to
learn from Erica Cruz versus somebody
else because I find her to be someone
I'm willing to champion. I see myself in
her. I want to root for her." And that's
the goal ultimately. Or Mike who joined
and was like, "But I want brand deals.
Like, can I do storytelling at brand
deals?" I'm like, "Of course. That's
what every brand wants. Brands want
faces to tell stories about their
product. That's it. That's what these
brand deals are all about. Mike got a
collaboration with DJI because of his
storytelling content. Valentina made
$10,000 from our digital product and
brand deals. $10,000 by storytelling.
So, she was offering these services of
UGC work. She started services around
her digital product where she was
helping people market her world um of
different digital product businesses.
So, that's where her world is. She
started telling her story and all of a
sudden she grew followers. All of a
sudden people started to buy into her.
All of a sudden she's making more money.
But also what's really cool is if you do
this effectively, you don't even have to
convert as much. Like you don't have to
do as many conversion posts. Right now
you might be selling all the time. She
doesn't do that anymore, right? She can
do it once per week and immediately she
gets buyers because people want to buy
from her. It's because of her story. or
someone like Mal who sold 17 offers
organically in her content and even just
one one piece of content generated
$2,000 in affiliate earnings. That's
what storytelling does. People want to
buy into you, buy into the products that
you use, buy into your services, your
offers. Ultimately, she was able to sell
17 offers doing that. If you're somebody
thinking, "But June, I've never done
this before. There's no way that I can
post daily. I don't know how I would
edit in time. I don't know if I have any
of the bandwidth for it. Let me
introduce you to a few people. We have
someone named Miriam Becky who posted
daily for 30 days. 30 days straight and
got 105,000 views while having a
full-time job, while having a busy life,
while still being able to show up for
her family, while still being able to
show up for her passions. She just added
this because she's only spending 15, 25
minutes a day and she's able to make a
content piece because she knows the
templates. She knows exactly how to
execute it by telling her story as well.
Then Samantha, a gut health coach,
posted daily, sometimes twice a day. And
look at her views. In just a short
period of time, 42,000 total views,
1.8,000 interactions, 174 new followers.
Or someone like Samantha here as well, a
digital nomad, posted for 21 days. Here
we have Imman who has been able to post
for 30 days. or Leticia who had been
able to post for 37 days. Every single
one of them had the exact same concern
as you. I don't know how to edit. I
think I need more equipment, but you
don't need any of that. You just need
your phone and you just need a story to
tell. And I'm going to help you find the
story and I bet you have a phone, so
you're going to be totally fine to join
us at the storytelling content
challenge. Like this is cool. Like this
is like everyone's greatest fears. The
thing is is like right now everything
that you're feeling right now, you think
it's a sign that you're doing something
wrong, that this isn't the right time
for it. But it's actually a sign that
you're exactly on the right track. Every
successful person that you look up to,
there's nothing different between you
and them. The only thing different is
that they were willing to make a
decision when they didn't feel ready.
They just made the decision to be ready.
And over time, they've gotten so much
distance from you because they're
actually having so much compounding
results. And that's what you're going to
see here. If you decide to join us,
you're going to learn so much and your
skills can get so much better. Maybe day
four feels a little shaky, day seven
feels a little shaky, but by day 18, by
day 17, by day 21 as you go on after the
challenge, like you're going to have
these resources for lifetime. You can
continuously be a learner and it's
literally $349
for $15,000 worth of value. What more
could you need as a sign to say that
this is the thing for you to join? I
hope that you think of this as an
investment for your own future outcome.
Here's everyone who joined even
yesterday alone. We have Return to
Sovereignty Leseawn Woods. We have
Jennifer West. We have Manique. We have
Steven Tran. We have Jacqueline Castro.
We have Dr. Reeb. We have Marta, Amanda.
We have Michelle. We have Sam. We have
Gulam. We have Carolyn, Jared, Tricia,
David, Teemo, Jamie, we have Tim, we
have Coach Kinsey, we have Midlife
Strength, another coach. But everyone's
starting at different spots. This
person's about to hit 10,000 followers,
40,000 followers. This person has 550
followers. This has 140 followers. This
person has 133 followers. This person
has 616, right? 55 followers. Brand new
account. So, you can go ahead and do
this from scratch alongside us. And this
is the perfect opportunity to do so here
at the storytelling content challenge.
So again, for the two live lessons, the
three content guides, the ultimate
content playbook, the AI storytelling
coach, the stories that sell, the
private community, the storytellers
toolkit, the 21 days of daily teaching.
You do not have to pay the $15,000.
You can join this for just $349
if you invest with us today.
Does storytelling actually sell? Will I
get clients, leads, and sales from my
storytelling content I post during the
challenge? Of course, it's fundamentally
how you do top offunnel. It's
fundamentally how you get people to buy
into you. Like the easiest way that I
can think about this is like what is a
product that you've bought in your life?
What is a service or offer that you had
bought? And think about why you had
bought it. Probably because maybe word
of mouth, maybe a referral, maybe you've
heard their content, maybe it was an ad
of theirs, maybe you like them. But at
the end of the day, what happened is
that you trusted them. You trusted them
enough to pay money to them. It's not as
if there aren't other experts in the
space. Of course, there are. I'm moving
right now. I'm going and relocating. And
right now, there are like 100 moving
companies that can go through. I chose
one person out of like 34 calls because
I liked the person. It's not as if they
didn't offer the same services. Of
course, they did, but I liked the
person. I had a feeling an association
with that person. It's trust. But
ultimately building trust with word of
mouth and constantly telling people
onetoone is very difficult. It's
exhausting. The only other option that
you have are paid ads and that's
expensive. But right now with an organic
post completely free for you, you can
have one storytelling post that scales
your trust to thousands of people all
across the world that could potentially
buy from you. That is storytelling. It's
building trust. And whether you have
something to sell or you don't have
something to sell, it's totally fine
because ultimately, if you even want
brand deals, for example, you're
building the right audience. No matter
if you're going to sell something of
your own or you're selling someone
else's product through a brand deal,
ultimately you need trust and you need
the right audience. The best way you can
do that, the most honest and earnest way
that you can do that is through
storytelling because you don't have to
overthink it. You don't have to do a ton
of research. You don't have to do any of
that stuff. It can literally just speak
to your younger self version of you. And
ultimately you can go and build that
kinship, build that right audience and
be able to post content that builds um a
business behind it too. Isn't
embarrassing to share story in front of
competitors when I'm an entrepreneur?
It's up to you to choose the right
stories, right? So like let's say you're
a relationship coach. If you're a
relationship coach, you obviously don't
want to make content about how you're a
sucky partner. But maybe what you do
want to say is because of this past
month and you pouring so much into your
clients, you've realized it's made you
feel less present in your relationships
and now you're trying to gain an
awareness of it and you're actually
using your methods and now you've
actually turned that into another
healthy moment for both you and your
partner. So you could share that story.
It feels real. It feels human. It feels
honest. And ultimately it builds your
trust. You could tell, let's say if
you're a real estate agent, yes, you're
not going to tell a story about how you
screwed over a client, but you could
tell a story about how you became a real
estate agent and uh ultimately it drives
a lot of passion for you because you
love meeting people. You love presenting
um a home, a dream home of theirs. You
love making that connection. So, if you
told those stories, you feel real and it
builds your credibility and you start
stand apart from your competition. So,
it's about choosing those right stories
to tell and you're definitely going to
have that within the storytelling
content challenge.
If you're someone not comfortable
oversharing, do not worry. So, this
isn't about making traumab content by
any stretch of the imagination. It's not
even about you needing to talk about any
struggle. If you don't want to talk
about a personal struggle in that way,
it could even be a big ambition, right?
So, let's say for me, I had a big
ambition to build a storytelling content
challenge. And that's going to be hard.
There's no way I'm going to build this
really cool idea or product without me
going through a lot, right? So, I'm
showcasing that. It's not necessarily me
trauma baiting about my past, but it's
talking about an ambition of mine.
Right? So, you can choose whichever
stories you want to respectively tell.
You just got to find meaning in them.
How can I tell my story without naming
other people or confidential info? So,
when you tell stories, it's not about
other people. It's about your own
evolution. It's about your own
maturation. It's about your own mental,
physical, and spiritual transformation.
So, let's say if you are telling content
about a breakup, for example, that is
really hard, right? So, maybe you went
through a divorce or something like
that. You obviously don't want to put
the other person into your content. You
might not even want to put your family
or your kids at all in that content.
But, good for you. You don't need to.
You see, you could tell the exact same
story, but focus it on your own
perspective. So, maybe it's this idea of
never standing up for yourself, and now
you have stood up for yourself, and you
become more confident. Maybe it's this
idea of finally putting your own needs
first. So you made a decision. Now you
lead a life that's more aligned to you.
Maybe it's something along the lines of
you actually having a dream of yours to
start a family. So you decide to do so,
but it's taught you so much about how
you are as a man or as a woman or
whatever. It you can do this entirely on
your own perspective. So if you look at
my content for example, you might know
that I have a girlfriend. You might know
that I have a dad. You might know that I
have a sister and brother. But you don't
know anything about them. You don't know
their names. You don't necessarily know
how old they are. you don't know what
they do for work. And that's intentional
because all my story-led content is
about how I've evolved from that
circumstance. And that's how you can
actually tell really good stories
without putting anyone under the bus.
That's the goal.
Will I show you how to make content?
Literally, yes. Every single day, I will
literally walk you through how you edit,
how you script the post. I'm going to
give you a template for it as well. So,
all you have to do is follow it and I'm
going to show you how you can embed your
own story into it. So, I'll prompt you
for it and things like that. So, um,
it'll be super easy for you to apply
even for a pure pure beginner.
Okay? And I want you to think about
right now, imagine
21 days from today. Think about it. 21
days from today, are you going to be
stuck in that exact same spot as you
currently are right now? Not sure of
what to post. Burned out from trying
everything but nothing working. Not
posting for two weeks at a time until
you find motivation again. being stuck
at 200 views or in 21 days finally
having a method you actually understand
having 21 posts having your perfectly
aligned audience and proof to yourself
that you can physically do this like
this is what the storytelling content
challenge can ultimately do um and I
want to be doing it alongside you as
well so this should be a lot of fun so
someone says what if someone already
like themselves have two business pages
so if you have multiple accounts how are
you able to build another personal brand
on top. I would ask you how much is
those two business pages actually
earning for you? And I would think about
the cost of your time and energy and and
it not being displaced in the right
direction. I actually would fully argue
that you should go ahead and build a
personal brand and you should do the
other two posts. It's just like
portfolio pictures, pictures that you
have of testimonials, reviews, and
clients like that. And I put all of your
energy um into your personal brand
because through your personal brand, you
can funnel into two separate businesses.
You can even tag those two businesses.
You can do collab posts on those two
businesses. But people will buy into
people. So the amount of effort and work
that you would take to build a business
page across those two, if they're going
to be good business pages, is so much.
And if you could pour that same energy
into building a personal brand, you'll
grow significantly more and make
significantly more amount of money. So
that's what I would recommend you to do.
And that's why the storytelling content
challenge is going to be great for our
wonderful business owners, but also
people that don't have anything to sell
yet. um it is perfect for you because
you'll build the right audience.
Um someone said what do the different
colors on your wall mean? So event early
on it actually meant the different types
of people that were joining. So all the
people in pink for example all the
people in pink there were beginners. All
the people in orange were more inter
immediate to advanced. And then all the
people in blue were
specifically
like business owners. So business
owners, the coaches, we had people like
that. So, but what happened is I ran out
of sticky notes and um therefore they're
all turning into orange. But we got more
posts coming uh soon. Um,
so I am a mom and I am going ahead and
uh sailing. What do I do for my own
account? If we need to go to personal
names, we average about 10,000 views per
post. Yes, I would just go ahead and um
I think probably your username should
include your name in some way. Um I
think it's the best way, especially if
it's a personal brand. It should be for
you. Uh I
uh
Okay, Manique says, "I'd like to believe
that these are real people, genuine
people."
Um okay, so someone doesn't Manique
doesn't believe that Crystal and um
Susie were real people. Um I've never
met Crystal or Susie beforehand.
I'm sure that they can attest. Okay. Um
All right.
How would I change from a business
account to a personal brand? I mean, I
think you could just totally just make a
new account. Like, you don't even have
to transition that account into it. You
can just make a new account and you
could start that with the 21 days. Um,
no problem at [clears throat] all. It
could be an old account as well. Um,
okay, cool.
Unless I win. Okay. If I joined through.
Nice. All right. So, how is it that a
personal brand can actually lead into
like a b business page like in terms of
the traffic for it? There's a few ways.
One is you could literally have the
founder at in your bio. So, you can
actually list your account that way. Um,
if you wanted to, you can do
collaborative posts. So, you can
basically collab with your business page
on a specific um content and that means
that both of you your both of your
handles are going to be listed there.
Um, so yes. Okay. How about if you are
somebody that um [clears throat] Oh,
okay. Brenda says, "I am a cosmetologist
and I have my own studio. I had two kids
and since then my business hasn't been
thriving as it did before. I haven't
been posting. I don't know what to post
about since I don't know how to start my
own personal brand and link to my
business." So, Brenda, I would go ahead
and not just show your work. I would
teach and I would also show a little bit
about how you're doing these things. But
then more importantly, I would talk a
little bit about the why. Like, why is
it that you have your own studio? like
what is the joy that you get behind it.
So I think the easiest differentiator is
like just don't teach only about the
what show the why and that why is
ultimately your story. So is it that you
want to actually you know you really
enjoy this thing you have doing it for a
long time like what are the challenges
of owning a studio um and you can choose
stories that actually aid in your
credibility right so like let's say you
say things like like here's the story of
me trying to upgrade my studio because I
want to give my clients the best
services possible even that will be much
more engaging than you solely showcasing
some specific work around let's say like
lash tech work right it's significantly
bigger than that if you told stories
about why you even became a
cosmetologist in the first place or
let's say why you're doing this is like
you love your family, you want to do in
support of them. Um, all of those
reasons will bring new people into your
world that will eventually buy from you
as well. Um, so what I would do if I
were you, I would make a personal brand
and I would start an account that way.
Put your name on it. I would put your
business name in the the bio and I would
have a story highlight that includes all
of your services as well. Um, but people
will buy into people so you need to get
people in that way.
Um,
is it better to post to a personal
profile or uh like let's say a dual
account? I definitely I I would normally
recommend a personal page. It's just
yours. Um, in some cases you can do it
like with your partner for example. I've
seen that work, but normally it's one
person per account. Um,
uh, do story posts matter? So you mean
like the actual features of Instagram
stories? They do matter, but it doesn't
really matter that much until you have a
consistently engaged audience. So,
storytelling content is going to get
those consistently good engaged posts
and then ultimately you can use like
Instagram stories like the feature to to
try and sell it to them as well. Um, but
yeah, the feed posts definitely matter
more cuz that's the thing that's
bringing new people in. If we want to
keep the same account for business and
personal brand, what is a good content
ratio? So, that's a really good point,
Lexi. I would probably think that
majority of your content has if you're
going to do it on a business page. So it
depends like if the name is underneath
the business name then it depends and
then if it's under your personal name
you're adding your business service
that's different. I would recommend that
it's under your like if you're starting
this I would do underneath your name and
then you have the products let's say as
a service or whatever the thing is uh on
a story highlight and your pin instead
of post can be talking about that
service right uh let's say if you're
doing it first on a business page though
then the ratio would be like more like
three personalled content but it still
has to be continuously about the
business like about you as a founder
about the decisions that you're making
things like that and the other four can
be more about clients could be more
about the process behind behind the work
that you do. Uh, it's a good ratio. Remy
says, "Do I really need a niche?" Of
course you don't. Right? So, the whole
point of storytelling is that you don't
need a niche, that you are the niche
that ultimately you can tell stories
about your life. But it makes sense.
It's like I think the thing that you're
thinking right now is like, I think
about a topic and I'm going to talk
about and teach about that topic. But
that's not what storytelling is. It's
about seeing that topic as a vessel, a
medium in which you can present that
message. So if you are somebody that is
interested in let's say um fashion as
long as let's say you tell your
perspective on it you can go ahead and
talk about food you can go ahead and
talk about being a cosmetologist you can
talk about being Asian like you can talk
about those things because you are the
common denominator now naturally if you
are a business owner you will skew
towards your business and that's fine
but still you want your personal stories
like you being a business owner the
actual hardships that go through it or
all the aspirations and ambitions that
you have behind it Your face should be
part of it and that's what will get
people to buy into um your services too.
Uh would you suggest showing yourself
even if you have not reached some of
your personal goals? Of course, Jen,
like the whole goal is for you to bring
people into your journey and that is
storytelling. And if you don't have an
accomplished set of skills yet or
expertise, that's totally fine. You can
start making content exactly as you are
right now.
Um cool,
I guess. Um,
is
is storytelling always attract content
or can it be nurturing, position, and
convert? It can be nurturing, position,
or convert. It just depends on how you
execute it. So, like basically
throughout the actual 21 days, you're
going to see some posts that are meant
for higher engagement, which would be
like nurturing led stuff. You're going
to see content that is made for more
converting stuff, as in like if you have
a lead magnet, perfect. or if you don't
have a lead magnet and you want to
convert them um to like engage on your
post, things like that, there's
different ways to do it. But yes,
storytelling is fundamental to how we
kind of do all things, but mainly it's
going to be to attract new people, no
doubt.
Um,
cool.
Uh, do I think posting three to five
times a day is normal? Nope. You don't
need to do that. You just need to post
once per day. And I'm going to show you
how to do that. Um,
someone says, "Is it a good idea to
share personal stories even if they can
potentially offend some people? Should
you keep it not too personal?" Um, the
thing is is that your story should be
about your own evolution, right? So like
the goal is for you to talk about not
let's say someone else or let's say not
talk about a specific experience so
harshly. It's just talking about your
own transformation, your own emotional
maturation, your spiritual
transformation, your physical
transformation. There's so many examples
of this. Like let's say that um I'm
looking at my wall right now and I see a
Arya on my wall. Arya diverse. Arya
diverse might say, "Okay, I have a story
about how my loved one passed away." But
they don't want to talk about the loved
one passing away. They don't need to.
They don't even have to ever bring up
that event alone. They could talk about
the emotional maturation of like what
did that loss actually cause them to
think. Maybe it's the fact that they
were go going so fast in their lives and
they never actually took the time to
slow down and think about what's
important to them and they don't even
have to use the death. They can actually
just talk about their own realizations.
The problem could be I feel like I'm
moving too fast to even know what I want
in life. The pursuit could be and now
every single day I'm actually going to
take 15 minutes away from all things and
actually allow myself to be alone in my
own thoughts. Then the payoff could be I
don't have it all figured out, but I'm
trying my very best because if I don't
have purpose, I feel like none of this
is meaningful. Problem, pursuit, payoff,
right? It's the whole thing. But you
would never talk about the death if you
don't want to talk about the death.
That's how you can make content that is
still personal, but in a way that
doesn't offend anyone. It's like the
whole idea of like storytelling versus
oversharing. We want to storyt tell. We
don't want to overshare. Um, that's a
big thing, by the way, within the
storytelling content challenge. There's
an entire video about how to not
overshare, what it means to tell stories
versus oversharing and what are the fine
lines between them because you want to
protect yourself as well. Um,
so Valerie says, "I feel like after
these 21 days, we can literally start
building and monetizing." Yeah, no
doubt. Like if you want to, you can you
will have an audience now that's aligned
to you and then ultimately you can go
ahead and and build a product if you'd
like to. No doubt about it. Um, but
storytelling is the best way to grow to
your first 10,000 followers. And those
10,000 followers would be fully aligned
to you. It's not going to be people
aligned to a topic or anything like
that. So, the issue is if you niched
down today and you chose a specific
topic and you didn't listen to me and
you try to educate on a topic, even if
you grew 10,000 followers, it does not
guarantee that you're going to stay with
that topic for longer than 6 months. So,
what happens then if you transition into
a different topic? Well, no one's going
to engage with that material because
they only care about the information. If
you can lead with storytelling for your
first 10,000 followers, you can take it
wherever you want. If you want to focus
on a certain segment of your story so
they can build a business around it,
then you can do that and those people
will carry alongside you. That is the
power of storytelling. Um, cool.
Um, June, realistically speaking, how do
you consistently get so many views and
followers? I mean, one thing is it took
me a while to get there, right? for me
took me about like a year and a half for
me to see any type of traction. So, it
wasn't overnight for me. And then, not
only did it take me a year and a half,
but then took me about 2 and 1/2 years
to realize that I wasn't doing it as
optimally as I should be. I actually
didn't build the right audience for the
most part. And I had to then trace my
steps backwards. I had to restart in
many different ways on the same account.
And that cost me a lot of time and
energy. And that's why I'm trying to
then speedrun this for you and give you
exactly what you should be posting on a
regular basis so that you don't have to
overthink or make the same mistakes. So
that is the storytelling content
challenge in a nutshell. It's because I
want you to have the exact same results
but in a fraction of the time. Kenneth
just says there's $4,000 courses out
there that don't even have a fourth of
the value. I hope the rest of you still
think that this is for you. Um because
the storytelling content challenge I I
think you're going to be seeing it
everywhere and this should be a lot of
fun for all of us. So yeah, thank you
guys so much from the bottom of my
heart.